好的 来看看我们在哪
Okay. Let's see where we are.
我们可以移开这个 丢掉那个 弄掉那个
We could move this, get
rid of that, kill that.
我有点被吓到了 不需要她 那个也弄掉
That kind of freaks me out. Don't need her.
We can get rid of that.
搞定 好了 我们可以就这样开始了
That's done. Okay, we could start with this.
我知道这很有难度 但是大家伙儿 这就是网络
I know it's a hard-hitting piece,
but come on, you guys, it's the Internet.
我们需要流量 流量 更多流量 你有什么想法
We need traffic, traffic, traffic.
What do you got?
- 这个怎么样        - 完美
- How about this?  - It's perfect.
现在 她看起来足够有脑去搞定移民法案吗
Now, doesn't she look smart and
knowledgeable about immigration reform?
- 是      -是 是 她确实是的 对吧
- Yeah.   - Yeah, yeah. She does, right?
我逗你们玩呢 这不是成人网站
I'm fucking with you people.
This isn't a porn site.
我们是什么 到处找咪咪看的宅男吗
What are we, nerds trying to look at boobies?
继续看
Come on, Keep looking.
靠 哈喽
Shit! Hello?
嘿 宝贝 你在哪 还在工作吗
Hey! Baby, where are you? Are you still at work?
压根没呢
No! Not even close.
你知道吧 电影还有10分钟就开演了
Just so you know,
the movie starts in 10 minutes.
- 我知道 给我你的裤子          - 啥
- I know! Give me your pants. - What?
- 明天请你吃午饭 赶紧的                  - 不要
- I'll buy you lunch tomorrow. Come on. - No.
我是你老板 给我你的裤子
I'm your boss. Give me your pants.
请别迟到 我可不喜欢错过片头
Please try not to be late.
I really hate missing the beginning.
我知道 我知道
I know. I know.
给我你的裤子 我来了 宝贝
Give me your pants. I'm coming, baby.
马上就到了
I'm almost there!
- 还有多远       - 好像我都看见你了
- How far away?  - I think I see you!
- 你在哪啊 我在这           - 我也在
- Where are you? I'm here.  - So am I.
人真多 你穿的什么啊
So many people. What are you wearing?
我是影院外唯一穿着衣服的人
I'm wearing the only clothes
outside the theater,
因为外头就我一个人!
because I'm the only person
outside the theater!
我爱你这身打扮 看起来太性感了
I love that outfit.
You look so sexy in that.
你知道我很喜欢这部电影
You know that I love this movie.
如果一个妓女和一个无情的商人能坠入爱河
If a prostitute and a ruthless businessman
can fall in love,
那又有谁不能呢
then anyone can.
我知道这对你意义重大 所以对我也是
I know this means a lot to you,
which means it means a lot to me.
哼 明显对你不是
Well, apparently it doesn't.
我正看着你呢 可以看见你了
I'm looking at you right now.
I can see you!
Jamie
Jamie!
嘿
Hey!
- 嘿     - 你赶上了
- Hey.   - You made it.
- 是啊 嘿     - 嗨
- Yeah. Hey.  - Hi.
- 抱歉我迟到了    - 没事 我买了三明治
- Sorry I'm late. - It's okay. I got us sandwiches.
给你买了无谷蛋白火鸡面包 不含奶酪
I got you turkey, no cheese,
gluten-free bread.
你确定这里边不含坚果吧
You sure this was prepared
in a nut-free facility?
是的 我很了解我们的过敏史
Yes, I'm full aware of our allergies.
嘿 我来了 我来了 我很抱歉
Hey, I'm here! I'm here. I'm really sorry.
我们错过了>
We missed Your Body Is a Wonderland.
好吧 一首歌而已 也不是很糟糕呀
Okay. Only one song.
That's not so bad, right?
这可是他妈的>啊
It was fucking Your Body ls a Wonderland!
呃 好消息是他还有其他好歌啊
Well, the good news is,
he has so many good ones.
这样吧 下次别给我玩迟到 直接拉炮屎在我脸上更好
Here's an idea: next time, instead
of being late, just shit on my face.
因为这和错过>是同一种感觉啊
'Cause that's kind of the same thing
as missing Your Body ls a Wonderland.
好啦 来吧 我们得赶紧进去了
Okay, come on. We really gotta go in.
茱莉亚罗伯茨要穿上她的长筒靴了
Julia Roberts is about to put on
her really tall boots.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
我们暂时分开一下吧
I think we should take a break.
我感觉 我们得分开一阵子 你知道吗
I just feel like we should chill for a while, you know?
- 你确定要这么做吗        - 要跟我分手吗
- You're doing this? - You're breaking up with me?
你说过我是你的灵魂伴侣
You said I was your soul mate.
有吗 什么时候
I did? When?
当我们在床上边吃早餐边做爱的时候
When we were at that bed and breakfast
having sex.
- 但是 你知道的 那并不...         - 并不什么
- But, you know, that doesn't... - That doesn't what?
- 不算   - 我工作实在很忙 我很抱歉
- Count. - I was tied up at work. I'm sorry.
或许你应该少关心点工作
Maybe you should care
a little bit less about work
多关心关心你正在交往的女孩
and a little more
about the girl that you're dating.
因为据我所知 工作不能保证你
'Cause last time I checked,
work doesn't reassure you
喜欢被人从后面捅并且还不是基佬
that liking a finger up your ass
doesn't make you gay.
我没让你往里捅啊
I never said "go up." Okay?
我只说了轻轻的在周围就好
I just said lightly around...
It's like a little button.
我告诉你 这不关你的事了
You know what? Not your issue any more.
这就是你为什么迟到吗
Is this why you were late?
你一直在想怎么跟我分手吗
You were worried
about how to break up with me?
没 没 我在犹豫穿什么衣服好
Oh, no, no. I was trying to decide what to wear.
- 所以你就穿着连帽衫和运动鞋来了            - 是呀
- So, you went with sneakers and a hoodie. - Yeah.
完了你还打算这身打扮去参加体育生高考测试还是怎么着
What, are you gonna
take the SATs after this?
别发飙嘛 好吗
Don't lash out, okay?
- 你是个好妹子              - 姐才不是
- You're better than that. - I'm really not.
我只是觉得我们渐行渐远
I just think
we're heading in different directions.
是啊 你去了约翰梅尔的音乐会 而我没去
Yeah, you to the John Mayer concert
and me not.
顺便感谢你在音乐会开始之前跟我分手了
Thank you for doing this
before the concert, by the way.
有史以来最棒的分手
Best breakup ever.
他就是我们这个时代的雪儿克罗
(90年代以来最受欢迎的摇滚乐女歌手之一)
He is the Sheryl Crow of our generation!
我能问你个简单的问题吗
Let me just ask you a quick question.
顺便告诉你 分手了我也完全不会伤心
And just know that I am not at all
crushed by this breakup.
所以 诚实点告诉我 为什么要分手
So, be honest. Why?
- 等等 这是什么诡计吗     - 不是
- Wait, is this a trick? - No.
只是单纯的人类学研究
Just pure anthropological research.
好吧 你想找人谈恋爱
Okay. You want someone
to sweep you off your feet,
但是你只对谈恋爱本身有兴趣
but you're more interested
in getting swept off your feet
而不是和人谈恋爱的人
than the someone who's doing the sweeping.
表面上你以为都能处理得很好
You seem like you've got
it totally together,
实际上感情却很受伤
but you're actually
really emotionally damaged.
然后你的那双大眼睛有时候着实会吓到我
Also, you have, like, really big eyes,
and that freaks me out sometimes...
谢谢 理由很充分
Thank you. That's enough.
分手完全不是因为你
It is not you at all.
当然是我 你不正和我分手吗
Of course it's me! You can't say that.
You're breaking up with me!
不是 是我的原因 我不再喜欢你了
It's not. It's me.
I don't like you any more.
这是我的错 你应该得到比我更好的男友
This is my fault.
You deserve better than me.
你是个好人
You're a great guy.
只是有点不会把握感情 如果你问我的话
A little too emotionally unavailable,
if you ask me.
我没问
I didn't.
我很想做回普通朋友
I really want to stay friends.
- 那就做朋友吧        - 好啊
- Let's stay friends. - Sure.
完全没问题
Totally.
约翰梅尔
John Mayer.
约翰梅尔我来啦!
John fucking Mayer!
过来
Come here, you.
你会没事的
You're gonna get through this.
为什么感情开始时都是那么有趣 接着就变得这么操蛋了呢
Why do relationships always start off so
fun and then turn into suck-a-bag-o-dicks?
我真不能再相信这种充满好莱坞式陈词滥调的真爱故事了
I really have to stop buying into this
bullshit Hollywood cliché of true love.
闭嘴 凯瑟琳 海格尔 你这愚蠢的骗子
Shut up, Katherine Heigl! You stupid liar!
以后我只管工作和做爱 就像乔治克鲁尼那样
I'm just gonna work and fuck.
Like George Clooney.
我要把自己的感情封闭起来
I'm just gonna
shut myself down emotionally.
就像乔治克鲁尼
Like George Clooney.
哈喽
Hello.
请坐直 先生
Seat up, please, sir.
那是哈德逊河吗
Is that the Hudson River?
不是 那是东河
No. It's the East River.
那我们不会降落在上面吧
So we won't be landing on it, then,
like that flight,
就像被授予勋章的飞行员开的那架一样
you know, with that captain
they keep giving medals to?
那个飞行员是个英雄
That pilot was a hero.
混蛋
Asshole.
飞机真是事多
Plane actually did a lot of the work.
我想我找到了适合GQ杂志那份工作的完美人选
I think I found the perfect guy
to fill that job at GQ.
没 他提早到了 我正争分夺秒赶过去呢
No, he's landing early. I'm scrambling.
没 他还没接下工作呢 但是我会把他带过来的 放心
No, he's not sold on the job yet,
but I'll get him there. I always do.
我现在还穿的一身休闲装呢
I'm even picking him up in a hybrid.
他从洛杉矶来的
He's from LA.
I figured he's into all that bullshit.
嘿 先生 那座建筑是什么
Hey, sir, what's that
tall building over there?
帝国大厦
Empire State Building.
不 不 不 另外一座
No, no, no, no. No. The other one.
很高很高而且上面有天线有窗户的那座
The really, really tall one
with the antenna on top of it, the windows.
那就是帝国大厦
That is Empire State Building.
喔 是的 你说的没错 金刚嘛
Oh, yeah. You're right. King Kong.
嘿
Hey...
噢 你好 这个你用完了吗 见到面了吧
Oh, hey! Are you done with this?
All met up?
太好了 欢迎来到纽约 Penderghast女士
Great. Welcome to New York,
Ms. Penderghast.
恩
Yeah.
噢 不 不好意思
Oh, no. Excuse me. Sorry.
- 能把包递给我吗           - 当然 哪一个
- Can you hand me my bag? - Sure. Which one?
- 有肩带的那个              - 好的
- The one with the straps. - Okay.
给你
There.
好的
Okay.
- 谢谢       - 欢迎来到纽约 先生
- Thank you. - Welcome to New York, sir.
- 不好意思   - 恩恩
- Excuse me. - Yeah.
-这是我      -哪个 蓝色还是黄色的
-That's me.  -Which one, the blue or the yellow?
不是 用口红写的临时接机牌上的名字 就是我
No. The makeshift sign made
out of lipstick, that's me.
- 你是Dylan Harper     - 正是
- You're Dylan Harper. - I am.
我是Jamie Rellis
I'm Jamie Rellis.
- 你是来接我机的                              -你好 是的
- You're picking me up from the airport. - Hi. Yes, I am.
你总是这样接机吗
You always pick people up like this?
是啊 我喜欢制造乐趣
Yeah, you know,
I like to keep things interesting.
- 欢迎来到纽约         -  谢谢
- Welcome to New York. - Thank you.
你并不像是猎头啊
You're not exactly what comes to mind
when you think headhunter.
是啊 我更喜欢"招聘主管"这个词 猎头听着有点恐怖
Yeah, I prefer "executive recruiter."
Headhunter sounds a little creepy.
你跟踪我六个月 这才恐怖呢
You did stalk me for six months.
Kind of creepy.
来 来 来 我来拿
Here, here, here, I'll take it.
你真打算帮我拿包啊 你是那种女孩吗
You're really gonna carry my bag?
You're that girl?
不是 我是改变你人生的那种女孩
No. I'm gonna change your life.
I'm that girl.
我的生活已经足够好了
My life is already pretty great.
噢 是吗 生活足够好那你也不会来这里啊
Oh, really? 'Cause you wouldn't be here
if your life were already pretty great.
我才不会傻到拒绝免费游纽约
A free trip to New York.
I'd be an idiot to turn that down.
呃 那之前六个月你都是傻子了呀
Well, then I guess you must have been
an idiot for the past six months.
是啊 还有人说我傻得更久呢
Yeah, a lot of people
would say longer than that.
Dylan 这是个大机遇
It's a huge opportunity Dylan.
GQ杂志的艺术总监职位 强强联合啊
Art director of GQ magazine.
This is the big leagues.
不过我无意冒犯你的博客
I mean, no offense to your little blog
on the Internet.
我的博客上个月可是拥有六百万的点击率
Which got six million hits last month.
放一个我用咪咪搅蛋糕糊的视频在博客上
I could put up a video of me mixing
cake batter with my boobs
我就能赚到八百万点击率呢
and it will get eight million hits.
已经有人拍了 Dunkin-My-Tits-Hynes.com
It's been done. Dunkin-My-Tits-Hynes.com.
真的吗
Really?
好吧 你看 你的天赋毋庸置疑
Well, look, there's no question that
you are talented at what you do,
但这可是GQ呀
but this is GQ.
纽约太拥挤了
New York's so crowded.
看看吧 我是洛杉矶人好么
Look around. I'm from LA, okay?
- 我喜欢开阔的空间        - 你是瞪羚吗
- I like my open spaces. - What are you, a gazelle?
你到底在担心什么啊
Come on,
what's really worrying you about this?
不知道 我不想一下子得到爬得很高很高
I don't know. I don't want to be the guy
who took something legendary
我怕摔得会很惨
and shit the bed with it.
Excuse the expression.
好吧 那就别摔下来啊
Well, then don't be the guy who shit the bed.
Excuse the expression.
勇敢向上攀吧
Be the guy
who made the bed legendary again.
听着 面试之前我们先喝点咖啡 你会没事的
Listen, we'll get some coffee in you
before the interview. You'll be fine.
抱歉 不喝咖啡 还是喝点绿茶 抽根大麻的好
I'm sorry, not coffee.
Some green tea, soy, organic hemp bullshit.
纽约真热
Really hot in New York.
洛杉矶不热吗
Doesn't it get hot in LA?
是啊 洛杉矶也热 但是因为湿度的原因
Yeah, it gets hot in LA,
but it's the humidity.
在洛杉矶 如果是90度 那感觉起来就是90度 但是
In LA, if it's 90 degrees,
it feels like 90 degrees. But...
- 是啊   - 如果在纽约
- Right. - If it's hot in New York,
温度是90 感觉起来就像100000度
it's 90 degrees, it's like 100,000 degrees.
这关于天气的谈论真是太棒了
This conversation about weather
is really fascinating,
幸运的是 我们到了
but lucky for me, we are here.
那祝你好运
So, good luck.
不管怎样 我说过我不想要这份工作
Whatever happens, happens.
I told you, I don't really want it.
帮个忙总行吧 装装样子 起码让我这个猎头看起来专业呀
Just do me a favor?
Act like you do so that I look good.
- 那倒是可以     - 好 那去吧
- I can do that. - Okay. Go get 'em.
认识你很好 顺便说下
This is great, by the way.
看着点
Watch it!
- 嘿    - 你还在这
- Hey!  - You're still here?
是啊 这就是我的工作啊
Yeah. Well, it's my job.
不错
Nice.
那说说进展如何
So, tell me, how'd it go?
他们信了 你还能安全一阵子
They bought it.
You're safe for a little while longer.
谢谢 我欠你个人情
Well, thank you. I owe you one.
你发来的
This is from you.
你的录用通知
It's your offer.
- 等等 我拿到职位了吗  - 他们5分钟之前打来电话了
- Wait, I got it?    - They called about five minutes ago.
恭喜 午夜之前不给答复就算过期哦
Congratulations. Offer expires at midnight.
为什么你不亲口告诉我反而要发短信呢
Why didn't you just tell me
instead of texting me?
因为更具有戏剧性啊
'Cause it's more dramatic.
Dylan 你能胜任的
Dylan, you are not gonna shit the bed.
我见过你的作品 棒极了
I've seen your work. It's amazing.
这可是个大动作啊
It's a huge move.
你会为了一份工作而从此改变自己的人生吗 老实说
Would you uproot your entire
life for a job? Be honest.
呃 不会 为了一份工作可能不会
Well, no. For a job, probably not.
但是为了来纽约 是的 我应该会
But for New York? Yeah, I would.
我没让你去接受这份工作
Which is why I'm not gonna
try to sell you on the job,
而是要让你接受纽约城
I'm gonna sell you on New York.
纽约啊
It's New York!
我看过>
I've seen Seinfeld.
不是什么狗屁旅游版本
Not the bullshit tourist version.
装可怜呢你 有你的
Puppy dog eyes. Nice touch.
是啊 来吧
Yes! Come on.
我请你喝东西
Let me buy you a drink.
怎么了
What's wrong?
你在等什么
What are you waiting for?
灯还在变呢
The light to change.
你们洛杉矶人真可爱
You LA folk are so cute.
来吧
Come on.
来啊 没事的
Come on, it's fine.
- 看吧    - 恩
- See?    - Yep.
我要死了
I'm gonna die.
我们有布鲁克林大桥 曼哈顿
Here we have Brooklyn Bridge,
downtown Manhattan,
前面还有一间露天酒吧
and right in front of us, an outdoor bar.
喝酒喽
Alcohol. Now we're talking.
知道吗 我喜欢你
You know, I like you.
我是来让你做选择
I'll give you your choice of closes.
- 关于什么  - 我是怎样让你接受这份工作的
- What? - How I close you on this job.
- 好     - 阿谀奉承的方式
- Okay.  - So we got the flattery close.
Dylan 你真是太棒太专业了
Dylan, you are so good at what you do.
要不要随你的方式
The take-it-or-leave-it close.
老兄 我才不管你是否接受 反正我都能领到钱
Man, I don't care if you take it.
I get paid regardless.
让人同情的方式
The sympathy close.
你瞧 我的肾快不行了...
You see, my kidneys are failing...
为什么女人总认为唯一能让男人做她想让他做的事的方式
Why do women think the only way
to get a man to do what they want
就是去操纵他
is to manipulate him?
历史 个人经验
History. Personal experience.
Romantic comedies.
你来这总有原因的 不管你承不承认
Come on, you're here for a reason,
whether you want to admit it or not.
是啊 来看看我有哪些选择总可以吧 谁不想先看看
Yeah, to explore an option.
Who wouldn't want to know their options?
处在完美的状态的人
Someone who's in the perfect situation.
你呢
Are you in the perfect situation?
工作吗 当然是
Job? Absolutely.
其他事情呢 就不管你事了
Everything else? None of your business.
Shaun
Shaun!
- Jamie   - 嘿
- Jamie!  - Hey!
- 嘿 最近怎么样 宝贝    - 你在这干嘛呢
- Hey, what's up, baby? - What are you doing here?
- 肖恩怀特(滑雪滑板运动偶像)?   - 你看起来真棒
- Shaun White?                 - You look great.
- 最近有锻炼吗?        - 没 在大吃特吃
- You been working out?  - Nope. Just been eating a lot.
- 好吧   - 恩
- Okay.  - Yeah.
- 要喝一杯吗         - 好呀
- You want a drink?  - Yeah!
- 我去给你拿一杯 好吗            - 好的
- Let me get you a drink. Yeah?  - Okay.
- 当心 当心点         - 不好意思
- Careful! Careful.  - Sorry.
嘿 老兄 刚那像是空翻加旋转1260度啊
Hey, bro, that was like
a double McTwist 1260.
- 是啊  我喜欢恶作剧      - 是啊 我是Dylan
- Yeah, like the trick.  - Yeah, yeah, yeah. Dylan.
Jamie 能趁我没打烂他的脑袋之前
Jamie, you want to get this guy
out of my face
把这家伙拖出我的视线吗
before I break his fucking skull?
不好意思 老兄 没有侮辱的意思 我是你的超级粉丝
Sorry, bro. No disrespect. I'm a huge fan.
你根本不认识我 老兄 别装作跟我认识一样说话
You don't fucking know me, man!
Don't talk to me like you know me!
你以为我滑雪滑坏脑子了吗
What, you think I'm all chill
'cause I snowboard and shit?
再说一个字 我就爆你的菊
One more word,
I'll fuck you up like dynamite!
爆菊?
Dynamite?
开玩笑呢 老兄
I'm just playing, bro.
Jamie的朋友就是我的朋友
Any friend of Jamie's is cool with me.
- 没事的 老兄         - 没事
- It's all good, man. - All good.
你死定了
I'm whispering in the ear of a dead man.
待会见
I'll see you later.
- 很高兴认识你      - 拜 甜心
- Good to see you.  - Bye, honey.
Shaun White看起来真不错
Shaun White seems really great. Nice dude.
- 再说一下你怎么认识他的      - 姐破了他的处
- How do you know him again? - I took his virginity.
那你们应该认识很久了吧
So you guys have known
each other for a while?
也没啊 貌似8个月吧
No, it was like eight months ago.
哇
Wow.
他下面也有染"发"吗
So does the carpet match the drapes?
茂盛着呢 如果你懂我意思的话
It's hardwood floors,
if you know what I mean.
老天啊 恶心
My God! Terrible visual.
开玩笑的 他是我一个老友
Totally kidding, by the way.
Just an old friend of mine.
你们用同一种护发素吗
You guys use the same leave-in conditioner.
他头发真不错
His hair had nice body.
请来两份六号烤肉 多加酱
Can I get two gyro number sixes,
extra sauce?
- 你在看什么                -  警察
- What are you looking for?  - The cops.
- 来        - 警察?
- Come on.  - The cops?
是啊
Yep...
来吧
Come on!
- 你要带我去哪              - 一会你就知道
- Where are you taking me?  - You'll see.
这就是你要的室外空间
Well, here's your open space.
跑吧 羚羊 跑啊
Run, gazelle. Run!
- 哇 真是难以置信             - 我知道
- Wow. This is unbelievable. - I know.
好吧 这不是宋飞正传
Okay, this was not on Seinfeld.
说说 你老爸会怎么想
Come on,
what's your dad think about all this?
关于什么
About what?
他应该会有评价吧
Well, he must have an opinion.
他曾给洛杉矶时报供稿23年
He used to write for the LA Times
for 23 years.
某人功课做得很足哦
Somebody did their homework.
我有个叫谷歌的工具
I have this thing at work.
It's called Google.
他怎么会看待你这份工作
Come on, what's he think about the job?
事实上我没问他
Actually, I didn't ask him.
那你应该知道他会怎么说
Well, then you must know what he'd say.
他会告诉我 鼓起勇气去闯 无论我做什么他都会为我骄傲
He'd tell me to go with my gut and that
he'd be proud of me no matter what I did.
像是个不错的人
Sounds like a really great man.
是啊
Yeah, he is.
嘿 想看好东西吗
Hey, do you want to
see something really cool?
我从来都喜欢看很酷的东西 是什么呢
I always want to see something really cool.
What...
来啊
Come on.
好吧
Okay.
整个城市里只有这能真正看到星星
Only place in the city
you can actually see the stars.
- 哇   - 恩
- Wow. - Yeah.
- 太酷了               - 是啊
- It's pretty awesome. - I know.
我喜欢来这上面思考
I like to come up here to think.
当下面生活压的我有点透不过气的时候 它就像...
Just when it gets a little too much
for me down there, it's like...
就像纽约版的山顶
It's like my New York version
of a mountaintop.
最好的一点是 不用接手机
Best part, no cell reception.
每个你招募到的人你都会带到这来吗
You take all your recruits up here?
说真的我还没带任何人上来过
Actually, never really
taken anyone up here.
- 真的吗    - 是啊
- Really?  - Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
如果你跟人谈今天的事 我就把你的耳朵切下来
If you tell anyone about this,
I will rip your ears off
然后钉在你脖子上
and staple them to your neck.
整个城市的人都好暴力啊
Everyone in this city seems really violent.
来吧 我们走 最后一站
Come on, let's go. One last stop.
- 我刚感觉舒服一点了呢
- 我知道 赶紧的 老兄
- We're just getting comfortable.
- I know you are. Come on, buddy.
这是纽约啊 给我赶紧的
It's New York. Now hustle. Come on.
- 快点快点          - 你带我来看时代广场啊
- Come on, come on. - You're showing me Times Square.
- 一点都不好玩啊              -闭嘴
- This is not touristy at all! - Would you shush? Come on.
我们必须到哪都这么走这么快吗
Do we have to power-walk
everywhere we go?
是的
Yes.
每个人想到哪就去哪喽
So everybody just kind of walks
wherever they want, then.
就这怎么样
How 'bout right here?
- 啥意思            - 到了 就这
- What do you mean? - We're here.
噢 老天 1988年的歌啊
Oh, my God, it's 1988.
好了 小聪明 等一会儿
All right, smartass, give it five seconds.
- 这是什么       - 快闪族啊
- What is this?  - It's a flash mob.
- 像奥普拉秀      - 确实
- Like on Oprah! - Exactly.
我们要让开来吗
Should we get out of the way?
不 不 好好享受吧
No, no. Enjoy it. Take it all in.
- 真他喵的酷             - 是吧
- It's pretty damn cool. - Right?
酷毙了
It's kind of rad.
这些人这么做有钱拿吗
Do these people get paid for this?
没 他们这么做只是为了好玩
No. No. They kind of just do it for fun.
身上其中的快乐感觉真不错
It's nice to feel
like you're a part of something.
在纽约其实有时候也会很孤独
New York can be a little
bit lonely at times.
那你还让我来纽约啊
And you're trying to sell me on it.
无论哪里有时候都会感觉孤独啊
Every place can be a bit lonely sometimes.
- 当心       - 老天
- Be careful! - Oh, my God.
- 蹲下来       - 好的
- Come down. - Okay.
- 靠 弯腰              - 好的
- Shit. Get back down. - Okay.
- 我加入 - 啥
- I'm in.  - What?
- 你舒服我了      - 真的?
- You sold me.  - Really?
- 我接受这份工作     - 噢 天哪
- I'll take the job. - Oh, my God!
- 啥 你很惊讶吗
- 不 不 噢 你会爱上它的
- What, are you surprised?
- No! No. Oh, you are gonna crush it!
棒极了
Amazing.
- 大家可以回家了 谢谢你们           - 真有趣
- You can all go home now! Thank you! - Very funny.
来
Come on.
恭喜
Congratulations, sell-out!
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
我想说的是 飞机在河上迫降
All I'm saying is,
it wasn't so much the pilot's skill
比起飞行员的技术 飞机本身的性能也很关键
that landed that plane on the river
as much as the mechanics of the aircraft.
你意思是Sully机长并非英雄
Are you saying
that Captain Sully wasn't a hero?
不 不是
No, no.
还有各方面的因素啊
There were just other factors.
你不是美国人吗
Are you not an American?
嘿 混蛋 你倒是赶紧把你的东西从我车上拿走啊
Hey, fuckface, you want to get your shit
out of my car or what?
我...好的
I... Yeah.
欢迎来到纽约 擦你妹的...
Welcome to New York. Go and fuck a dick.
擦
Fuck.
那么 我要求的只是你们大家给我一点时间来赢得你们的信任
So, all I ask is that you give me
a little bit of time to gain your trust.
我知道我是个新来的 但是我会用陈词滥调来弥补我的经验不足
I know that I'm new at this, but what I lack
in experience I make up for in cliches.
所以 我的门永远都是开着的
So, my door is always open.
严肃的来讲 我的门想关都关不上
But seriously, my door is always open.
我生意上的第一个订单就是 一扇轻点的门
My first order of business, lighter doors.
- 好了 谢谢大家       - 欢迎你 Dylan
- Okay. Thanks, guys. - Welcome, Dylan.
嘿 伙计 我是Tommy Bollinger 运动版的编辑
Hey, man. Tommy Bollinger, sports editor.
Tommy 我读过你的文章 喜欢你的作品
Tommy, I've read your articles.
Love your writing.
只是尽量保持真实
Just trying to keep it realsies.
听着 我想晚上带你出去搞搞基
Listen, I'd love to take you out one night
and troll for cock.
- 啥?   - 你们洛杉矶的帅小伙很多
- What? - You got some pretty boys out there in LA,
但是纽约的小伙子质量更棒啊
but the quality in this town is ridiculous.
我们一起去见识下
We can tear this shit up.
我不是基 Tommy
I'm not gay, Tommy.
真的吗 我以为搞艺术的都... 你懂的
Really? I just assumed,
art director and, you know...
嘿 不摸
Hey. No skin, more pipe for me.
顺便 我想写篇关于冰球场上种族歧视的文章
By the way,
doing a piece on racism in hockey.
想听听你对于字体上有什么好的想法
Love to get your concepts on the font.
我需要好的建议
I'm thinking Helvetica
but I could be persuaded to Courier New.
我自己又知道些什么呢 我只是个运动版的编辑
But what the fuck do I know?
I'm just the sports editor.
- 你确定你不是基?           -确定..
- You sure you're not gay? - Yep.
- 我确定    - 好吧
- I'm sure. - Okay.
好吧
All right.
- 嘿   -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
我想敲门 但是你根本没有门
I'd knock, but you don't have a door.
- 没有     - 没
- I don't. - No.
嘿 看看这个
Hey, check this out.
人奶蛋糊面包.com
Dunkin-My- Tits-Hynes. Com.
- 恩 确实有这么个网站
- 我说了嘛 但是不是那个 是这个
- Yeah, it really does exist.
- I told you, but not that. This.
真棒
Awesome.
但是如果这样的话 会更棒
But it'd be even more awesome
if this happened.
等着
Wait for it.
真好看
Nice!
我跟一个快闪族组织者联系过了
I got in touch with a guy
who puts flash mobs together.
我们要借用他们来做游击式广告
We're thinking about using them
for guerrilla advertising.
把单纯的东西加以商业化利用?
Taking something so pure
and commercializing it?
就知道我找对了人
Knew I found the right guy.
- 我来了     - 这是你的合同
- Here I am. - Okay. Here's your contract.
签完字我就可以走了
Sign it and I will be out of here.
好的
Okay.
一整年?
A whole year?
为什么我觉得这是你的第一份工作
Why do I get the feeling this is the first
real commitment you've ever made?
不是啊 我曾在T-Mobile工作了两年
It's not. T-Mobile, two years.
靠 我真后悔那两年
And, fuck, do I regret that one.
帮帮忙 别一年之内就辞职或者被炒掉
Do me a favor. Don't quit or get
fired before the year's up,
因为那样我就得不到额外奖金了
because otherwise I don't get my bonus.
等等 我想走就能走?
Wait, I can leave whenever I want?
- 那这份合同有什么意义
- 你就赶紧签了吧
- What's the point of this contract?
- Just sign the damn thing.
好吧
Okay.
共事愉快 Dylan Harper
Nice doing business with you, Dylan Harper.
嘿 我正打算吃午饭呢 你有好地方吗
Hey, I was thinking of getting some lunch.
Do you know a place?
你这是要约我出去吗
Are you asking me out?
呃 不是
Whoa, I'm not asking you out.
只是想让你带我去个餐馆
I'm asking you to show me a restaurant.
我是你在纽约唯一的朋友
I mean, I'm the only friend you have
in New York.
- 你不想把关系复杂化吧
- 我知道 我不是要和你约会
- You don't wanna complicate that.
- I know. I'm not asking you out.
我意思是 当然 我们能到处找乐子
I mean, sure, we'd have fun, roll around,
- 然后开始想着上床                        - 上床?
- get into some erotic humiliation fantasy. - Erotic?
但是最终糟糕收场 从此形同陌路
But it'd all blow up in our faces, end badly,
and we'd never speak to each other again.
我他妈的不是想约会你! 我发誓
I'm not fucking asking you out!
I swear to God!
好吧 你不喜欢我
Okay. You don't like me like that.
那你也不用这么凶吧
You don't have to be so mean about it.
对不起 我不是那意思...
I'm sorry. I didn't...
天哪 你真像个女孩子 走吧 我请客
God, you're such a girl.
Come on, it's my treat.
来纽约工作没那么难吧
So was it an easy move?
- 难的是要离开我老爸           - 是啊
- It was tough leaving my dad. - Yeah.
我姐姐说了一大堆
My sister gave me some shit.
不过真是时候
But timing was right.
还真是时候
Timing was really right.
- 那是你姐姐吗         - 不 是我前女友
- Is that your sister? - No. My ex.
她不太正常 超爱约翰梅尔
She's great. Loves John Mayer.
分手后还希望我们能做朋友
Wants us to stay friends.
她确信自己能治好我的感情障碍
She's also convinced she can cure me
of my emotional unavailability.
- 你有感情障碍                     - 噢 是啊
- You're emotionally unavailable?  - Oh, yeah.
噢 天哪 我是感情受挫 我没在聚会上见过你啊
Oh, my God. I'm emotionally damaged.
I haven't seen you at the meetings.
我不想再谈什么感情了
I'm done with the relationship thing.
女孩 恭喜你没掉进恋爱的陷阱
Girl, you are preaching
to the congregation.
- 爱情   - 什么?
- Choir. - What?
是爱情的陷阱
"Preaching to the choir." You're supposed
to preach to the congregation.
- 要这么说才对
- 我懂我意思就行了
- That's the expression.
- Did you understand what I was saying?
别跟我咬文嚼字了
Then don't be a dick about it.
噢 天哪 你介意吗
Oh, my God. Do you mind?
- 请吧    - 很好
- Please. - Great.
你好 这是Dylan Harper的手机
Hello. You've reached
Dylan Harper's cell phone.
他的爱情已占线 但是...
He's emotionally unavailable,
but if you'd like...
- 我爱约翰梅尔!     - 哈喽?
- John fucking Mayer!  - Hello?
哇 喂?  移动真垃圾啊
Wow. Hello?
You really do have shitty cell service.
- 是吧      - 是啊
- Right?    - Yeah.
明天我会请一些朋友来家里
I'm gonna have some friends over tomorrow.
要不你也过来 然后见见新朋友?
Why don't you come,
and you can meet some new people?
我得查一下时间表 我太忙了
I'm gonna have to check my schedule.
I'm really busy.
我在GQ杂志工作 这可不是那些网络上的小博客
I work at GQ now.
It's not some little blog on the Internet.
- 嘿    - 嘿
- Hey.  - Hey.
- 你来了         - 抱歉迟到了
- You made it.  - Sorry I'm late.
不 不 请进 请进 谢谢
No, no. Please, come in, come in.
Thank you.
嘿 大家 嘿
Hey, everybody! Hey!
这是Dylan 从洛杉矶来的
This here is Dylan. He's from LA.
他来为今晚的啤酒买单的
He's the reason I can afford all this beer.
好的
Okay, all right.
我是种动物吗
Am I an animal?
是的
Yeah.
靠 玩这个我很在行的
Fuck, I'm pretty good at this.
Kali中尉是我5年认识的一个西海岸街头艺术家
Lieutenant Kali's a West Coast street
artist I got into about five years ago.
- 他的后现代艺术诠释                - 这玩意美极了
- His postmodern interpretation... - This shit is amazing.
我知道
I know, right?
你将能够找到适合贵公司职位的完美人选
You will be able to find the perfect candidate
to fill the position at your company.
好的 来看吧
Okay, here we go.
首先是Joey Morena 会流利的越南语
First up is Joey Morena,
who's fluent in Vietnamese
然后有着超过10年的烹调经验
and has had 10 years of experience
in the culinary field.
我不能这样下去了
I can't do this any more.
不 我觉得我们都需要各自去寻找快乐
No, I think we both need to go get happy.
一切都不再完美了
It's not adding up to a hundred any more.
是啊
Yeah.
看起来纽约到处都是蓝莓
Looks like New York's
all out of blueberries.
再见了 烙饼
Goodbye, Flapjack.
出租车!
Taxi! Taxicab!
烙饼
Flapjack.
为什么这些电影的音乐这么烂
Why do all these movies
have such bad music?
这样才能让你知道怎么去感受每一秒
It's so that you know how to feel
every single second.
"我的心碎了"
"I'm heartbroken."
"我嫁给了我的梦中情人"
"I'm getting married
to the man of my dreams."
"我正瞧瞧的溜过办公室"
"I'm sneaking through an office."
Madison 等等
Madison, wait!
Madison
Madison!
Madison 等等
Madison, wait!
Bryce
Bryce.
你怎么知道我在中央车站
How did you know
I was at Grand Central Station?
你在洛杉矶 电影就是在洛杉矶拍的
You're not. You're in Los Angeles,
where this movie was shot.
我比你自己更了解你
I know you better than you know yourself.
大厅对面的你那疯子朋友Susie告诉我的
And your crazy friend Susie
across the hall told me.
Susie
Susie.
为什么你在这
Why are you here?
为了告诉你
To tell you that
我爱那让你潸然泪下的夕阳
I love that sunsets make you cry
我不管你是否挂掉了房地产考试
and I don't care that you failed
your real estate exam,
我很高兴你有约会5次的原则
and I'm glad that you
have a five-date rule.
我爱你
And that I love you.
我更爱你
Not as much as I love you.
第五轨道爱情列车的乘客请上车
Now boarding, track 5, love.
天哪 我有时真希望我的生活也能像电影般美好
God, I wish my life was a movie sometimes.
我从来不需要为我的头发担心
You know, I'd never have to worry
about my hair,
也不用担心要去卫生间
or having to go to the bathroom.
然后 当我处在人生最低谷时
And then, when I'm at my lowest point,
会有人狂奔整条街到我面前 向我表白
some guy would chase me down the street,
pour his heart out,
然后我们就接吻
and we'd kiss.
从此幸福快乐
Happily ever after.
坐着四轮马车
I mean, a horse and carriage?
这太棒了
Come on, that is awesome.
那也比不上这首歌词含糊不清并且跟情节撘不上边的
Not as awesome as this
ambiguously upbeat pop song
的欢快嘻哈歌曲吧
that has nothing to do with the plot
他们把它放在最后 好让相信你度过了90分钟快乐时光
they put in at the end to try to convince you
that you had a great time at this shitty movie.
你知道为什么他们就从来不接着拍接吻之后的戏吗
You know, why don't they ever make a movie
about what happens after the big kiss?
拍的啊 那叫AV
They do. It's called porn.
天哪 我真怀念做爱的感觉
God, I miss sex.
是吧 我意思是 有时候人需要性爱 就像是
Right? I mean, sometimes you just need it.
It's like...
我不知道 就像是在拧脖子
I don't know, it's like cracking your neck.
为什么性爱总要伴随着其他并发症呢
Why does it always gotta
come with complications?
- 比如感情      - 还有罪恶感
- And emotions. - And guilt.
罪恶感
Guilt.
- 那是女人的错        - 什么?
- It's women's fault. - What?
你没听错 "抱着我 让我们一起白头偕老"
You heard me. "Hold me.
Let's spend the rest of our lives together."
噢 得了吧 你也好不到哪去
Oh, please, you are no better.
"噢 耶 宝贝 叫我的名字 耶"
"Oh, yeah, baby, come on, now.
Say my name. Yeah..."
"我到高潮了 我表现如何"?
"I'm done. How was I?"
你跟谁这样过?
Who have you been with?
为什么就不能不是那样呢
Why can't it not be like that?
这是生理反应 就像打网球
It's a physical act. Like playing tennis.
两个人就应该就打网球那样做爱
Two people should be able to have sex
like they're playing tennis.
是 我意思是 没人愿意打完网球之后
Yeah, I mean, no one wants to
go away for the weekend
离开一个星期
after they play tennis.
只是一场游戏 握握手 继续自己的生活
It's just a game.
You shake hands, get on with your shit.
- 是啊  - 是啊
- Yeah. - Yeah.
还要喝啤酒吗
Do you want more beer?
恩
Okay.
- Jamie   - 恩?
- Jamie!  - Yeah?
- 我们来打网球吧      - 啥?
- Let's play tennis.  - What?
我们来做爱吧 就跟打网球一样
Let's have sex like we're playing tennis.
别开玩笑
Get the hell out of here.
别笑 这也许会很棒
Don't laugh. This could be great.
也许能消除所有的尴尬
This could take all the
weirdness out of it.
我们谈过的 我不是那种意义上的喜欢你
Well, we talked about this.
I don't like you like that.
我也不是啊 这就是为什么我们的关系很完美
I don't like you like that either.
That's why it's perfect.
我都不知道你是否足够有魅力
I don't even know if I find you attractive.
做作
That's cute.
好吧 我有对付混蛋的方法
Well, I do have a thing for jerks.
好吧 那你觉得我有魅力吗
Okay, well, do you even find me attractive?
- 别做作了      - 不 不 不是
- That's cute.  - No, no, no.
在你见识我的人格魅力之前
Before you got to know
my awesome personality.
我的身体魅力如何
Strictly physical.
第一眼你见到我的时候
First time you saw me.
- 就我们两个讨论这事吧              - 是
- This is just two people talking?  - Yeah.
两个在Bennigan's喝醉的女孩  说吧
Two girls over drinks at Bennigan's. Go.
我喜欢你的眼睛 我从来没坚果这么大这么美的眼睛
I liked your eyes. I didn't think
I'd ever seen such big, beautiful eyes.
你的嘴唇 是的 我想你应该是个接吻高手
Your lips. Yeah.
I thought you might be a good kisser.
我是
I am.
- 你的胸部       - 怎么样
- Your breasts.  - What about them?
- 我被他们迷住了      - 真的吗
- They intrigued me.  - Really?
- 是的   - 我觉得他们太小了
- Yeah.  - I think they're so tiny.
- 小归小 但还是胸部啊       - 谢谢
- They're still breasts.   - Thanks.
- 我喜欢你的手         - 嘴
- I liked your hands.  - Mouth.
- 臀部     - 声音
- Butt     - Voice.
- 胸膛   - 双眼
- Chest. - Eyes.
- 你说过了        - 我认真的
- You said that.  - I meant it.
你发誓除了做爱 不会对我再有其他想法了
You swear you don't want anything more
from me other than sex?
你发誓你不想从我这得到更多
You swear you don't want anything
more from me?
我知道你们女孩子
I know how you girls get.
Tick-took, tick-took.
停
Stop it.
- 你要干嘛             - 拿出我的IPAD圣经
- What are you doing?  - I'm pulling up my Bible app.
- 你有IPAD圣经?          - 是的 我是个好女孩
- You have a Bible app?  - Yes. I am a good girl.
- 手放上来            - 好的
- Hand on the iPad.   - Okay.
等等 不
Wait, no.
怎么他们就不能搞定这个
Why can't they figure this out?
不 这玩意弄不清楚我跟你谁是谁了
No... This thing thinks
I'm you and you're me.
你手别动 我来调位置
Keep your hand still. I'll move the iPad.
- 这让我感觉有点晕                 - 坚持住
- It's actually making me dizzy.  - Hold on.
搞定了
There we go.
没有情人关系
No relationship.
不谈感情
No emotions.
就为了性
Just sex.
不管怎样 我们都是朋友
Whatever happens, we stay friends.
- 发誓    - 发誓
- Swear.  - Swear.
好了
Okay.
我觉得我们该开始了
So I guess we should just start.
好
Okay.
我先来
I'll serve.
这有点...  网球什么的够了
That's really...
That's enough of the tennis.
我们去卧室吧
Let's go to the bedroom.
沙发不行吗 比在床上更不会有感情
What's wrong with the couch?
It's less emotional.
卧室灯光好一点
The bedroom has better light.
正因为我们是朋友 我不需要为了我的身体而感到不安
And since we're just friends,
I don't have to be insecure about my body.
噢 你很美
Come on, okay? You're beautiful.
你没必要感到不安
You have nothing to be insecure about.
不 你看 这太感情化了
No, you see,
that is way too emotionally supportive
你必须封闭它
and you need to just lock that down.
- 你的屁股真小                - 哪有
- Your ass is a little bony.  - Much better.
我的胸部很敏感 我不喜欢听下流情话
My nipples are sensitive,
I don't like dirty talk,
早知道要这样 我就早上先把腿刮干净了
and had I known this was gonna happen,
I would have shaved my legs this morning.
我下巴很怕痒 有时候还会打喷嚏
My chin is ticklish,
I sneeze sometimes after I come,
早知道这样
and if I'd have known
this was gonna happen,
我就不会早上刮腿毛了
I wouldn't have shaved
my legs this morning.
好拉
Okie-dokie.
我要穿着袜子 有亲密感
I keep my socks on. Intimacy issues.
正好 因为我讨厌脚 老爸弄的
Great, 'cause feet gross me out.
Daddy issues.
很好
Great.
还行
I can work with that.
应该可以
Should be fine.
真不敢相信我这么做了
I can't believe I'm doing this.
要不别做了 出去跑个步
Should we stop? We could just go for a run.
我不知道 这么做会不会显得太老
I don't know, are we
getting too old for this?
- 做爱?    - 不 一夜情
- Sex?     - No, casual sex.
不知道 有点像回到大学时代
It just, I don't know,
feels a little collegey.
- 我来唱首歌吧                         - 行
- I could sing some Third Eye Blind.  - Okay.
- 你这唱的什么啊
- 歌啊
- That's not Third Eye Blind.
- I'm pretty sure that's Third Eye Blind.
不是
Nope.
- 怎么了          - 我们就只做一次
- What's wrong?   - We're just doing this once.
- 完全同意         - 好的
- I totally agree. - Okay.
- 好      - 好的
- Great.  - Great.
加快速度
Little faster.
- 快              - 看着我的下巴
- More circular.  - Watch my chin.
- 咬我的耳朵       - 好的
- Touch my ears.  - Okay.
吻我的脖子
Kiss my neck.
- 叫我的名字    - 小Dylan Francis Harper
- Say my name. - Dylan Francis Harper Jr.
别叫全名啊
Not my full name.
不好意思 我
Sorry, I had to fill out
a lot of your paperwork.
- 别说话          - 好的
- Stop talking.  - Okay.
噢 天哪 你真是
Oh, my God, you're really...
....................
A, B, C, D, E, F, G, H, I,
J, K, L, M, N, O, P...
- Dylan 我      - 放松
- Dylan, I...   - Relax.
朋友之间的性爱
Just a friend going down on another friend.
噢耶 宝贝 风卷残云
Oh, yeah, baby. Tornado.
啥跟啥啊
What, what?
你在干嘛 挖隧道呢
What are you trying to do?
Dig your way to China?
- 这个我很在行啊       - 谁说的
- I'm good at this.   - Says who?
跟我在一起的所有女孩子
Every girl I've been with.
好吧 要不她们说谎了 要不她们都是黑木耳了
Well, they're either lying
or their vaginas are made out of burlap.
放松 你又不是蜥蜴
So, relax. You're not a lizard.
- 好吧         - 好
- Okay, fine.  - Okay, fine.
- 往右一点                 - 好
- A little to the right.   - Okay.
- 再稍微往左一点                   - 收到
- A little bit more to the left.  - Roger that.
- 下来          - 来吧
- Now go down.  - Here we go.
-
- A little more... Whoa, too far!
- Sorry.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing!
你这么一叫 我以为...
When women start to scream,
it could be misconstrued.
继续啊!
Just keep going!
耶
Yeah, you know it.
Well, let me tell you how I like it.
See, most girls think
you should start off soft,
but if you just get in,
really go for it, ..
Yeah, you know it.
- 就用Obama吧          - 不 不 不
- Let's go with Obama.  - No, no, no, no!
这太简单没有内涵了 用Shaun吧
It's too easy, too predictable.
Go with Shaun.
他像神一样诠释运动的完美 身材又那么棒
He's stylish, transcendent of sport,
has an ass like a kumquat.
- 我听说他是个混蛋             - 不 他不是
- I hear he's kind of a jerk.  - No, he's not.
他只是威胁过你嘛
You're just threatened by him
因为他是世界上最好的运动员
because he's the greatest snow
sport athlete in the universe
独领风骚
and he gets more squirrel than an oak tree.
嘿 Dylan    Jamie在大厅等你
Hey, Dylan?
Jamie Rellis is in the lobby for you.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thanks.
午饭后我们再谈好吗
Let's hit this after lunch. Okay, guys?
没人对Obama感"性趣" 兄弟
Nobody wants to fuck Obama, brah.
瞧他那大象耳朵
He's got ears like an elephant.
又不是大象"鼻子"
That's not the part of
an elephant you want.
- 嗨    - 嗨
- Hi!   - Hi.
不好意思这么突然现身
Sorry to just show up like this.
不 不 没事
No, no, no, it's fine.
呃
So...
- 散不步?           - 好啊
- Wanna take a walk?  - Love to.
好的
Great. Okay.
关于昨晚发生的事 我....
Okay, so about what happened, I...
- 那太疯狂了 我们真不该那样的
- 确实不该
- It was crazy and we shouldn't have done it.
- Exactly. No, no, exactly.
我意思是 这太不像我风格了
I mean, it is so not me.
同意 我们忘掉它吧
I totally agree. Let's forget it happened.
好啊 你看 我们有了一夜情
Great. I mean, look,
I've had one-night stands.
不太光荣的一夜情 但是
We both have had one-night stands,
none of which we're proud of, but...
真的?
Really?
我们只是为了性
Look, to think that you and I
could just have sex
而没有爱 这样做..
and without it compromising anything
was just so...
- 是错误的     - 对
- Misguided.  - Exactly.
早上我打算给你打电话说的
I was gonna call you this morning.
但是你没有啊
But you didn't.
我没有
But I didn't.
你看 我们的关系已经不像以前了
And you see, it's already
coming between us and I really...
这不是我想要的
I just don't want it to.
不会的
It's not going to.
我表现很坚强 说话也很强硬 但是我..
Look, I know that I act all tough
and I talk all tough, but really...
只是为了掩饰你柔弱的内心
It's just a front to protect yourself
from your own vulnerability.
你是谁? 我的心理医生吗
What are you, my fucking therapist now?
不 我是你朋友 我知道你每次骂人都会眨眼
No, I'm a friend. Who knows that
every time you curse, you blink.
- 其实你不想骂人的                      - 没啊
- Like your body's rejecting the word. - It does not.
- 我靠         - 眨眼了
- Fuck you.   - Blinked.
- 我靠 我没眨眼                - 又眨了
- No, I didn't fucking blink.  - Blinked again.
- 擦       - 啊 这次没眨
- Shit.    - Ah, didn't blink.
说"擦"字还行
"Shit" you're okay with.
- 这太愚蠢了       - 是的
- It was stupid.  - Yes.
- 我们是朋友 一直做朋友
- 是啊 我可不想失去你这个朋友
- We're friends, let's stay friends.
- Yes. Yes, this, I don't wanna lose this.
我也不想
Me neither.
- 好       - 太棒了
- Great.   - Fantastic.
两位需要情侣画像吗
Portrait for the lovely couple?
- 我们这是在干嘛               - 我不知道
- What the hell are we doing?  - I don't know.
- 抚摸我的头发   - 吻我的脖子
- Rub my hair.   - Kiss my neck.
- 看着我的胸部       - 好 好
- Watch my nipple.  - All right, all right.
- 我不知道你还有纹身呢               - 是啊
- I didn't know you had a tattoo.  - Yeah.
怎么以前我没注意到
Why didn't I notice that before?
因为我们喝醉了
Because we were drunk.
- 这是你的狗狗        - 不是 没养过
- Was it your dog?   - No. Never had one.
其他人都养的啊
But everyone else did.
我以为养狗就代表有个正常的家庭呢
And I thought having a dog
meant you had a normal family,
17岁的时候我真的很想养一条
which at 17 I desperately wanted.
叛逆的你却纹身了
So as a sign of rebellion you got a tattoo
纹了一个很常见的东西
of the most conventional thing
you could think of.
那时候真是酷毙了
It was super awesome back then.
- 看         - 恩
- Check it.  - Okay.
- 一道闪电           - 18岁的时候
- A lightning bolt?  - Eighteen.
- 想拥有超能力         - 恩
- Wanted superpowers.  - Yeah.
那时候我很迷哈利波特
I was a little into Harry Potter back then.
- 那时候你是个基吗
- 谁说喜欢哈利波特就代表是基啊!
- Were you also gay back then?
- Harry Potter doesn't make you gay!
- 好吧     - 你确定要这样?
- Okay.    - Are you sure about this?
- 你呢        - 不
- Are you?    - No.
我也不确定
Me neither.
- 你今天过得怎样        - 还行
- How was your day?    - It was okay.
- 我中午吃了个火鸡三明治               - 味道如何
- I had a turkey sandwich for lunch.  - How was that?
很一般 你今天呢
It wasn't that good. How was your day?
还在研究地铁系统 比较难弄
Still trying to figure out that
subway system. It is tricky.
And it's out of here!
- 我的屁股   -什么?
- My butt.  - What?
- 噢 我的屁股疼   - 是嘛?
- Oh, my butt.    - Really?
我屁股快抽筋了 拿个枕头给我
No, I mean my butt, it's cramping.
Can you grab a pillow?
好 好
Okay, yeah, yeah.
- 不疼了吧        - 不了
- So, no butt?    - No.
- 真的? 这么快?      - 开玩笑
- Really? Already?   - Just kidding.
- 喜欢这个姿势吗             - 恩 还可以
- Do you like this position?  - Yeah, it's all right.
老实说 我有点萎了
I gotta be honest, I feel
a little emasculated.
女孩子脱光趴在你身上你却萎了?
A naked girl is lying on top of you
and you feel emasculated?
- 有点
- 你知道萎是什么意思 对吧
- Little bit.
- You do know what that word means, right?
我知道啊 我现在就这么觉得
Yes, I know what it means, and I feel it.
好吧 好吧
Okay, all right, you big baby.
- 换个位置             - 好的!
- Chinese fire drill.  - Okay. Go!
Okay.
- 雄起了吗?                - 是的
- Do you feel manly now?   - I do.
好的 放进来
Okay. Put it in.
这一点都不好笑
That's not funny.
- 有点意思             - 有点意思
- It's kind of funny.  - It's kind of funny.
- 等等        - 怎么了
- Hold on.    - What's wrong?
我得上一下厕所
I have to go to the bathroom.
- 啥 现在?    - 是啊 今天吃太多西瓜了
- What? Now? - Yes, now. I had a lot of watermelon.
你搞啥飞机呀
What's going on in there?
你知道小弟弟硬起来的时候要撒尿有多痛苦吗?
Do you know how hard it is
to pee with a hard-on?
不 不知道
No, actually.
就像被挤压的感觉 要很久的
It's like two lanes of traffic
merging into one. It takes time.
- 你在拉屎?          - 没啊
- Are you pooping?   - No.
- 那你为什么坐着               - 这样容易控制一些啊
- Why are you sitting down?   - It's easier to control.
- 难道你想我撒得到处都是吗    - 不 不 不 不好意思
- You want a mess in here?   - No. No, no. Sorry.
耶
Yeah.
咋了 我有洒出来吗
What? Did I leak?
洗手了没
Did you wash your hands?
噢 老兄!
Oh, come on, dude.
我知道我们是朋友 但我终归是个淑女啊
I know we're just friends,
but I'm still a lady.
给我把手洗了 然后再带着你的小屁屁来床上
Now get back in there, wash your hands
and then bring that fine ass back here.
你要是再这么说话 我就不来了
If you keep talking to me like that,
I'm not gonna come back.
- 疼死我了
- 吃个香蕉吧 在冰箱里
- My hammies are killing me.
- Have a banana, they're in the fridge.
你怎么把香蕉放冰箱里啊
Why would you keep bananas in the fridge?
- 会干掉的啊           - 不会的 香蕉有皮啊
- It dries them out.   - It doesn't. They have a peel.
又不是盔甲 空气还是会进去
It's not armor. Air still gets in.
你到底要不要吃香蕉
Do you want a banana or not?
如果是干的就算了 我又不是个动物
Not if they're dry. I'm not an animal.
至少我家还有吃的
At least I have food in the house.
你家就只有酸奶
All you have at home is drinkable yogurt.
我喜欢酸奶 不费时间
I like to drink my yogurt.
It's a timesaver.
那你觉得可以用省出的那点时间刮干净你的胡渣吗
Well, then you think you could use
that time to shave your stubble.
你的胡渣扎得好疼
Your whiskers are like knives.
看吧 如果你是我的女朋友 我肯定不能叫你闭嘴
Now, see, if you were my girlfriend,
I couldn't tell you to shut up right now.
正因为你只是我的炮友 我就可以告诉你
And because you're just my buddy,
I can tell you
如果你不刮胡子 我就不刮下面
that if you don't start shaving up here,
I'm gonna stop shaving down there.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey. Hey...
- 妈妈   -" 妈妈"?
- Mom!   - "Mom"?
我的眼睛闭着的  我没看见你们在干什么
My eyes are covered.
I don't know what you're doing.
我没看见你正穿着黑色底裤呢
I can't see you putting on
your black underpants.
Jamie 宝贝 我真想你
Jamie, baby, I missed you.
噢 宝贝
On, baby.
-你的胸部变大了?              -妈妈 我在这
-Did your boobs get bigger?  -Mom, I'm over here.
嘿 宝贝 噢 噢 他们没变大
Hey, baby. Oh, no, they didn't.
- 你来这干嘛
- Victor是个蠢货
- What are you doing here?
- Victor turned out to be a total Lombard.
L-O-M-B-A-R-D 人傻钱多
L-O-M-B-A-R-D.
"Lots Of Money But A Real Dullard."
Victor是他的未婚夫
Victor, her fiancé.
前未婚夫
Ex-fiancé.
- 怎么了           - 没怎么 他就是爱胡扯
- What happened?   - Nothing. He was just blah.
对牛弹琴
I mean, nice, but it was
like talking to dirt.
某天我醒过来我对自己说"Lorna"  我是Lorna
I woke up one day and I said, "Lorna..."
I'm Lorna.
- 我是Dylan  - 我说"Lorna, 这不是你的福气"
- Dylan.   - I said, "Lorna, this is not your bliss."
- " 你已经39岁了"                - 48
- "Just because you're 39..."    - Forty-eight.
"但不代表你需要就此安定下来 他不是什么好的归宿"
"...It doesn't mean you have to settle.
He's not an insurance claim."
所以我撘第一班飞机离开那个岛了
So I caught the first plane off the island.
- 克里弗兰市不是岛            - 噢 宝贝 它是的
- Cleveland's not an island.  - Oh, baby, it is.
不管怎样 我来了 很高兴看到你
Anyway, here I am. It's so good to see you.
你没说起过你有个帅气男友啊
You never told me you had a hot boyfriend.
他不是我男友 老妈
He's not my boyfriend, Mom.
- 是啊 我们只是朋友                   - 我喜欢
- That's right, we're just friends.  - I love it.
充满70年代气息
It's like the '70s in here.
那是个更好的时代 只为了性
That was a better time. Just sex.
怀孕的时候
A little grass, a little glue...
Not during pregnancy.
当然最后的时候就不能做了
Well, not during the final trimester.
不用有什么顾虑 太棒了
But no complications. It's great!
好吧 我们就是这样的
Okay, well, that's technically, I guess,
what this is.
就是这样
That's exactly what this is.
那我女儿就是你的泄欲工具了?
So my daughter is just your slampiece?
不 不 "泄欲工具"?
No, no. "Slampiece"?
开玩笑! 继续吧
I'm just kidding. Slam away.
玩得开心 我觉得这很棒
Have fun. I think this is great.
有一点就是 你不用再去商场购物了
The only thing is, it
takes you off the market.
去他喵的商场 既然你想要的都有了
But what the hell.
The whole reason you go to the market
为什么还要去买呢
is to buy the produce,
which you already got.
见到你真是太好了 宝贝 我只待几个星期就走
It's so good to see you, baby.
I'm only gonna be here a few weeks.
我快饿死了 有松子酒吗?
I'm starving. You got any gin?
在厨房里
It's in the kitchen.
你得走了
You gotta go.
- 她喷了香水吗                   - 我不知道 快走吧
- Is she wearing Axe body spray?  - I don't know. Come on.
香蕉放冰箱里? 你波多黎各人吗?
Bananas in the refrigerator?
What are you, Puerto Rican?
- 这么说不太好吧 老妈
- 开玩笑呢 你老爹就是波多黎各人
- That is terrible, Mother.
- Just joking. Your dad was Puerto Rican.
什么? 你说他是希腊人
What? You said that he was Greek.
- 土豆 土豆...          - 穿鞋
- Potato, potato...    - Get your shoes.
- 好 好               - 快走 快走
- Okay. All right.    - Well, not... Just go, just go.
我把他们放自行车上?
I'll just put these on on the bike?
- 是的      - 好吧
- Yeah     - Okay.
很高兴见到你
It was nice to have met you...
- 嘿       - 你脱裤子呢
- Hey.    - And your pants are coming off.
天哪  妈 ! 拜托
Oh, my... Mom! Mom, please!
Back, back!
That's what I'm talking about!
我们要打败所有的基佬
We're kicking every gay ass out here!
没有轻蔑的意思 有搞基的吗?
I don't say that pejoratively,
I say it hopefully.
等等 你是基吗
Hold it. Any of you gay?
- 你也不是?       - 得了吧 老兄
- Not even you?   - Come on, man.
等会我们谈谈 只谈5分钟就好
Come talk to me after.
Give me five minutes of your time.
你也许有理由让你相信
I might be able to let you see some reason.
真牛
Look at you in the house!
来吧 宝贝
Come on, baby!
我该去见Jamie了
I'm supposed to meet up with Jamie.
谁? 那个猎头?
Who's that, that headhunter?
咋 你们现在约会呢
What, you guys going out now?
不 不 我们只是普通朋友 关系有点乱
No, no, no, we're just friends.
We're messing around a little bit.
- 什么意思            - 睡在一起
- What do you mean?   - Sleeping together.
只是为了上床
But it's just sex.
行不通的 老兄
That never works, bro.
她是个女孩 性对她们来说重要得多 不管承认与否
She's a girl. Sex always means more
to them even if they don't admit it.
Jamie不同
Jamie's different.
难道她有小JJ?
Does she have a penis
where most girls have a vagina?
- 没有       - 那她就没有不同
- No penis.  - Then she's no different.
你又对女人了解多少啊
What do you know about women, anyway?
老弟 我吃过的盐比你吃的饭还要多好吗
Dude, I've turned down more tail
than you'll ever have.
是啊 老兄 但你是个基..
Yeah, bro. You're gay.
但是还是有很多人投怀送抱啊 看看我
But the offers still keep rolling
in, naturally. Look at me.
嘿 我喜欢女人 她们既庄严又神秘 既美丽又迷人
And, hey, I love women. They're beautiful,
majestic, mysterious, mesmerizing creatures.
既聪明睿智又善解人意 各方面比男人更胜一筹
Smart, empathetic.
Far superior to men in every way.
如果我有选择 我肯定会选和一个女人在一起直到死去
And if I had a choice,
I would be with women to my dying day.
但我是个基...
But me likes cock so I'm
strict-aly dick-aly.
所以说 一切不就只是为了性嘛?
So it's always just about sex, then?
不是 我也曾深爱过
No. I've been in love.
I went down that rabbit hole.
直到我发现了什么吗
You know what I discovered?
当你爱一个人 你会想着怎么跟她一起度过整个周末
It's not who you want to spend
Friday night with,
而不仅仅是星期五晚上
it's who you want to spend
all day Saturday with.
懂了吧
Feel me, Felix?
是啊 然后把生命中每一天都当成是周末
Yeah, but then it's every Saturday
for the rest of your life.
你现在不懂也没关系
It's okay, you don't get it.
没啥大不了的 你终究会明白的
It's no big deal. But you will.
终有一天 你将会遇到一个你深爱的人
One day, you'll meet someone
and it'll literally take your breath away.
爱到无法呼吸
Like you can't breathe.
Like no oxygen to the lungs.
- 就像一条鱼      - 好拉 我懂了 Tommy
- Like a fish...  - Yeah, I get it, Tommy.
不 你才不懂
Yeah, you don't.
早上的新网站做得很不错 顺便说下
Nice work on that new online site,
by the way.
页面头条的字体是什么?
What was the font on that headline?
是Times Roman字体
It was Times Roman.
Times Roman  不错 我走了
Times Roman. Inspired. I'm out.
你有船?
You have a boat?
我住在泽西城 我不搭轮渡
I live in Jersey.
And I ain't taking no ferry.
除非是去吃晚饭或者看表演
Unless it's out to dinner and a show.
- 嘿    - 啥
- Hey.  - Yeah.
你和那个Dylan 有性无爱的朋友关系 真不错
You and that Dylan? Way to go.
I mean the whole friendship-sex thing.
干得漂亮
Kudos, baby, kudos.
没什么大不了的
It's not that big of a deal.
我只是有点惊讶 我一直以为你是相信真爱的女孩
It's just surprising. I always thought
you were a true-love kind of girl.
不管怎么样 妈 这又不会影响我做其他事情
Whatever, Mom. It's not like
it's stopping me from anything.
78年的时候我也这么想的
That's what I thought back in '78.
之后也是
And every year since.
事实上我还是很高兴的
I'm just... I'm flattered, actually.
有其母必有其女嘛
The apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
只是有点点意外而已
It's just surprising.
- 好了 搞定                           - 恩
- There, done. It's... There we go.   - Okay.
看起来真漂亮 像个公主
You look great! You look great.
You look like a princess.
- 是      - 是吗
- Yeah!   - Really?
- 是啊    - 恩
- Yeah.   - Okay.
7月4号那天 我朋友把他在蒙淘克的房子借给我
Hey, my friend gave me his house
in Montauk for July 4th.
我们一起去那 远离尘嚣 远离男人
Let's you and me go away together.
No men, no bullshit.
就我们母女俩 跟>电影里的那样
Just mother-daughter.
Like a Nora Ephron movie.
上次我们母女共度周末是什么时候
When was the last time
we spent a full weekend together?
我8岁的时候 在佛蒙特 跟着一个滑雪教练
When I was eight, that time in Vermont.
We got snowed in with the ski instructor.
- Demitri    - 是Bill
- Demitri.   - Bill.
他让我想起了你父亲
He reminded me a lot of your father.
深色卷发 橄榄色的皮肤 冷战般的口音
Dark curls, olive skin, Cold War accent.
- 我父亲是俄罗斯人?        - 不记得了
- My father was Russian?  - I don't remember.
我只记得我们喝了很多伏特加 然后打了很多炮
But what I do remember is we drank
a lot of vodka and shot a lot of guns.
老妈 这个"谁是你父亲"的游戏越来越没意思了
Mom, this "who's your daddy" game
is getting really old.
我知道我不是世界上最好的母亲
I know I haven't been
the best mother in the world...
对不起 你在设套让我往里跳吗
I'm sorry,
were you waiting for me to jump in?
来啊 一起去吧
Come on! Go away with me. Come on!
去吧 去吧
Come on. Come on.
好 我去 会很有趣 是吧?
Okay, we'll do it. It'll be fun, yeah?
- 妈..     - 母女连心
- Mom...   - I was trying to bond!
都很好看的嘛
It was either this or sniff glue.
- 关于我妈的事 不好意思了 - 我觉得她很有趣呢
- Sorry about my mom.    - I thought she was funny.
是啊 她要钱的时候 特别有趣
Yeah, she's really funny
when she's asking for money,
她要来过来住的时候 更加有趣
and she's hilarious
when she needs a place to stay.
Dylan 我觉得我想重新开始约会了
Dylan, I think I wanna start dating again.
听着 我觉得我们不能再这样了
Listen, I think we should stop this.
是吗
Yeah?
我觉得你是对的
I kind of think you're right.
是吗
Right?
一扇门关闭 另一扇门又会打开
Every new beginning
comes from some other beginning's end.
这话确实有道理
That actually makes sense right here.
谁有能想到>这首歌如此有预见性呢
Who would've thought Third Eye Blind
could be so prophetic?
不是>
Not Third Eye Blind.
我很肯定是的
I'm pretty sure that's Third Eye Blind.
想去吃点午餐吗
Do you wanna go grab some lunch?
- 恩     - 好的
- Yes.   - Okay.
- 你买单           - 啥?
- You're buying.   - What?
好吧
Okay.
- 裤子     - T恤
- Pants.   - Shirt.
就这么结束了?
So this is the end of this?
- 我想是的 但这是好事            - 是啊
- I guess so. But it's good.     - Yeah.
- 目的达到了          -单纯上床 没有其他
- And we did it.     - With no bullshit.
- T恤        - 汗衫
- Shirt.     - Sweater.
我们还是朋友
We managed to actually stay friends.
- 是的    - 是啊
- Yup.   - Yeah.
那到底喜欢什么类型的女孩
Okay. So, what is your type, anyway?
没有固定的类型
No, I don't have a type.
- 我更注重内涵                    -噢 得了吧
- It's more about what's inside.  - Oh, please!
好吧 她怎么样
Okay, what about her?
恩 我可以去探究一下她的内心世界
Yeah. I could get to know her inside.
她正在阅读呢
And she's reading a book.
Nicholas Sparks的小说
It's probably Nicholas Sparks.
- 我去跟她搭讪               - 什么?
- I'm gonna go talk to her.  - What?
这么惊讶干嘛 不是说了我们可以再开始约会吗
What do you mean, "What?"
We said we wanted to date again.
- 我去了                       - 现在?
- I'm gonna go talk to her.   - Now?
当着这么多人的面?
Here, in front of all of these people?
我又不是要去强奸她 只是搭讪而已
I didn't say I was gonna rape her.
I said I was gonna go talk to her.
呃 我是Dylan 很高兴认识你
Excuse me. I'm Dylan. Nice to meet you.
"恋恋笔记本"
The Notebook.
很高兴见到你
Nice meeting you.
- 噢?     - 有说有笑
- Well?   - We talked. We laughed.
是啊
Yeah.
- 比利时人         - 难怪在看书
- She's Belgian.   - Explains the reading.
我告诉她露台在哪
I showed her where the balcony was,
她要在那和她丈夫碰头
because that's where
she is meeting up with her husband.
结婚纪念日到纽约来旅行
Anniversary trip to New York.
有3个孩子 Christof, Karlina 和 Pepijn
Three kids. Christof, Karlina and Pepijn.
闭嘴
Shut up.
有什么好笑的 至少我尝试了
Why are you still laughing?
At least I gave it a shot.
好吧 轮到姐出场了
Fine. I'll go next.
- 看我有没有戏                  - 好啊
- See if I still have game.   - Okay.
- 好   - 恩
- Okay.- Okay.
- 好     - 这 11点钟方向
- Yes.   - Right here. Eleven o'clock.
- 拿着冰咖啡      -貌似很帅 不过不知道
- Iced coffee.   - Handsome, but doesn't know it.
盯着树看 应该是来公园游览的
Staring at a tree, which means
he's actually in the park for nature
而不是来看美女日光浴的
and not to watch women sunbathe.
- 或许他是个弱智哦     - 我才不管
- Or he's retarded.  - Don't care.
我去了
I'm going in.
- 不好意思      - 恩?
- Excuse me.   - Yes?
- 你好    - 你好
- Hi.     - Hello.
我是Jamie
I'm Jamie.
恩 恩 可以啊
Yeah. Yeah, that works.
嗨
Hi.
好的
Okay.
- 很高兴见到你        - 噢 天啊
- Nice to meet you.   - Oh, my God!
他名叫Parker 是个儿科肿瘤医生
Okay. His name is Parker.
He's a children's oncologist.
周六我会和他约会
And I have a date this Saturday.
- 不错   - 谢谢
- Nice.  - Thank you.
为什么他朝我招手
Why'd you wave to me?
我告诉他你是同性恋 是我最好的朋友
I told him you were my gay best friend,
所以他想跟你和他的兄弟牵线搭桥
so he wants to set you up with his brother.
大学念的医学院 从那以后我就没睡过好觉
College, med school,
and I haven't slept since.
真不敢相信你找到了治疗癌症的方法
I can't believe you actually cure cancer.
上帝帮了我
Well, me and God.
- 什么?    - 我开玩笑呢
- What?    - I'm kidding.
有人会真的这么说啊
Can you imagine
someone who would actually say that?
有啊 我跟很多这种人约会过
Yeah, I could.
I've been out with a lot of them.
- 癌症医生?          - 不是 是混蛋
- Cancer doctors?   - No, assholes.
是啊
Yeah.
希望你跟他们没关系了
Well, hopefully you're all done with that.
别说我没提醒你 很多癌症医生都是大混蛋
Although, I gotta warn you,
lot of cancer doctors, big assholes.
- 真的吗    - 是啊
- Really?   - Yeah.
还有脑科医生 超级变态
And brain surgeons, huge perverts.
这里弄弄 那里弄弄
While they're doing this,
a little bit of that.
嘿
Hey.
谢谢
Thank you.
何时再能见到你啊
When can I see you again?
现在啊
Right now.
- 开玩笑             - 好吧
- I'm just kidding.  - Okay.
你能想象谁会这样说话呢
Can you imagine
someone who would actually say that?
高中我吹过大号
I played the tuba in high school.
世界上最醇的乐器了
World's stupidest instrument.
特别是当你搬了8次家
Especially when you move eight times.
- 为什么搬家
- 我老妈经常跟男人分分合合
- Why'd you move?
- My mom really likes to break up with guys,
她很擅长这个
and she was really good at it.
- 你父亲也是其中之一吗
- 不 不 他是很早以前的事了
- Was your dad one of them?
- No, no, he was long before that.
事实上我从来没机会认识我爸爸
I actually never knew my dad.
我很遗憾 那太糟糕了
I'm sorry. That sucks.
好吧 我觉得我应该告诉你一些事情了
All right, look, I think I should
probably tell you something.
别说你有小JJ啊
Please don't tell me you're a dude.
不然自从我来这之后 这是第三次了
Because that'll be like the third time
since I moved here,
我可再也承受不了了
and I don't think I can handle that.
我有个5次约会原则
I have a five-date rule.
- 你知道的 要约会5次我们才能...            - 恩
- You know, like, five dates before we...  - Yeah.
我在电影里见过 我想试试看
I saw it in a movie.
I thought I'd give it a try.
你值得我等待
You're worth waiting for.
我很肯定这也是那部电影里的台词
I'm sure that was the line
in the movie you saw.
真不错
That's awesome.
我给一个4岁的小孩做了几个月的治疗
This four-year-old that I've been
working on for the last couple months,
他马上就要康复了
he's gonna be fine.
- 那太棒了       - 是啊
- That's great.  - Yeah.
怎么你这样男人还是单身啊
How is a guy like you single?
我只是在公园里等待一个女孩的出现
I've just been waiting for someone
to come up to me in the park
然后夸我在看树而不是看美女
and compliment me for looking at the trees
and not the sunbathers.
我是认真的 给了我不错的印象
I meant it. It was impressive.
事实上 坦白的说
Actually, if I'm gonna be
completely honest with you,
我只是在站着打瞌睡
I was sleeping standing up.
我连续工作了36个小时 我都不知道我怎么就到公园里了
I worked 36 hours straight.
I don't even know how I got to the park.
你这样的女孩怎么也单身
How is a girl like you single?
各种各样的问题
I have issues.
貌似有人说我有情感病
One might even call me damaged.
事实上 确实有个人这么说我的
Actually, one did call me damaged.
别扯了 怎么个病法
Get out of here. Damaged how?
我比较相信真爱
I kind of believe in true love.
有个白马王子会来接我
That there might be
a Prince Charming out there for me.
盯着树看的那家伙怎么样?
听着 我知道你也许会说不 因为你跟木偶一样除了工作就是工作
Listen, I know this is probably a no
because all you do is work like a dull boy,
但是一起去喝一杯怎么样
but would you like to come get a beer?
不用了
I'm good.
又不是基佬酒吧
No, it's not a gay bar.
而且那还有很多帅哥靓妹哦
And there'll be just as many hot girls
as hot guys.
好吧 我去
You know what? I will come out.
好呀 去找个好女孩
All right. Let's find you a lady.
你还是不肯搞基 是吧?
You're still not gay, right?
- 不    - 好吧
- Nope. - Okay.
- 什么?   - 你知道今天什么日子吗
- What?   - Do you know what today is?
- 第五次约会          - 我都没在算
- Date number five.  - I wasn't even counting.
- 想去床上吗?                - 不 就这很好
- Wanna go in the bedroom?  - No. Here's fine.
很高兴今天遇到你
I am so glad I met you tonight.
我也是
Me, too.
你在想什么
What are you thinking?
在想你是多么棒
Just how great you are.
Annie 嘿
Annie, hey.
他喵的谁是Annie啊
Who the fuck is Annie?
我姐姐
My sister.
最好是 不然我切了她
Better be. I'll cut her.
当然 我马上就来
Of course I'm coming.
是啊 我4号请假 我会待3天
Yeah, I'm taking the 4th off,
so I'll be there for three days.
恩 爸爸怎么样了
Yeah. How's Dad?
恶化了吗?
Any worse?
恩恩 替我向他问好
All right, tell him I said hi.
拜 Banannie
Bye, Banannie.
我想跟你父母见面
I want you to meet my parents.
不.. 你? 确定?
No, you... Really?
天哪
God!
嘿 等下
Hey. Hold on, hold on.
别 等我一下下
No, just hold on. Just give me a second.
我找个地方说话
I gotta go find a place to talk. Okay.
靠 别挂
Shit. Shit. Just hold Oh.
- 噢 不好意思  - 别挂
- Oh, sorry.   - Hold on.
昨晚我很晚出去了
I was out pretty late last night.
回来的时候 看见你和你的女朋友在沙发上
When I got in, you and your girlfriend
were on the couch
所以我就倒在你床上了
so I just crashed in your bed.
- 他不是个女的        - 闻起来像
- He's not a girl.   - He smells like a girl.
- 你闻了他?          - 我想买棉花糖
- You smelled him?  - I wanna buy marshmallows.
- 你说什么?           - 周末去蒙淘克
- What did you say?  - For Montauk this weekend.
我想去露营 就像你小时候那样
I wanna do a campfire,
like when you were little.
好吧
Okay.
- 然后我们去找棒棒糖
- 好吧 棒棒糖
- And then we're gonna look for sticks.
- I hear you. Sticks.
然后我们再唱歌 我们再...
And then we're gonna sing. We're gonna...
等一下
Just hold on a second.
恩
Okay.
怎么了
What's up?
你觉得男人是关心全球变暖多点
Do you think guys care more
about global warming
还是会关心怎么穿着白色裤子去烧烤多点
or how to wear white pants to a cookout?
好吧 那要看情况
Well, that depends.
你有穿着比基尼的性感模特站在雪顶上的吗
Do you have a hot model in a bikini
standing on an icecap?
没 在滑道上
No. Ski slope.
我还是选穿白色裤子去烧烤的吧
I'd still go with pants to a cookout.
恩 我也是
Yeah, me, too.
你的Parker男孩怎么样了 还在盯着树看吗
How's your boy Parker?
Still staring at trees?
来两杯咖啡  是啊 还在看大树呢
Two coffees.
Yeah, he's still looking up at trees,
不过这次是在我家里看
but this time it's
actually in my apartment.
- 这么快就第五次约会了?         - 可能吧   谢谢
- It's the fifth date already?  - Maybe. Thank you.
那你们接下来做了?
Did you guys "fifth-date""?
- 你怎么这样!  好女孩才不会说呢
- 我知道 所以我才问你啊
- How dare you! A lady never tells.
- I know. That's why I'm asking you.
嘿 我得挂了 祝你洛杉矶之行愉快 下飞机记得打电话给我
Hey. I gotta go. You have a great
trip in LA and call me when you land.
好吧
Okay.
Parker
Parker.
嘿
Hey.
我买了脱脂咖啡 加了一份白糖 一份Splenda( 一种甜蜜素)
I got us coffees.
Nonfat, one sugar, one Splenda.
- 我得走了           - 什么?
- I gotta get going. - What?
我以为你今天都不需要当班呢
I thought you weren't on call today.
是不需要 但我有....有点事...
I'm not, but I got that thing...
I got stuff.
医院刚打电话来
This... They just called me.
- 真的吗?   - 是啊
- Really?   - Yeah.
偷偷溜走 真是够俗套的
The sneak-out.
How incredibly cliché of you.
我只是..
I just...
我只是觉得我做不了你的白马王子
I don't think I can be
your Prince Charming.
天哪 你根本没弄懂我的意思
God, you totally didn't get
anything that I was saying, did you?
- 不 不 不 我觉得你很棒              - 是啊 你也是
- No, no, no. I think you're great.  - Yeah, you, too.
嘿 那我们做朋友怎么样
Hey, you know what?
You and I should stay friends.
- 真的吗?  - 假的! 去你大爷
- Really?  - No, go fuck yourself.
谁能站着睡觉啊
Who sleeps standing up?
你应该为我感到骄傲啊
You know, you'd be really proud of me.
我骂他的时候我都没眨一下眼哦
I didn't even blink
when I told him to go fuck himself.
- 你刚就眨了
- 这不算 现在又不是当时
- You did just then, though.
- This does not count. I'm not in the moment.
我不明白 或许我床上功夫太差
I don't know, maybe I suck in bed.
相信我 你不差
Trust me, you don't suck in bed.
- 谢谢        - 真是缺爱的孩子
- Thank you.  - So needy.
嘿 也许那个人已经结婚了什么的呢
Hey, maybe the guy's married or something.
没 上班时查过他的背景
No, did a background check at work.
单身 没有犯罪记录 信用状况不错
Single, no criminal history,
credit report 720.
背景调查 你查过我吗
Background check. Did you do one on me?
你居然能刷爆Old Navy的信用卡
How could you possibly
max out an Old Navy card?
大学毕业之后 我很喜欢cargo的裤子啊
After college I was
really into cargo pants.
Dylan 我得继续从我这找原因
Dylan, I gotta stop thinking it's not me.
- 我意思是 肯定是我的原因     - 不是的
- I mean, it's gotta be me.  - It's not you.
你没有什么不正常的啊
Nothing is wrong with you.
他是个男人 你给了他5次约会才能上床的考验
He's a guy.
You gave him a five-date challenge,
把你上了 然后闪人  忘了这混蛋吧
he got you and cutout. Forget the douche.
他就是个十足的混蛋
He's a dick. He's a dick-douche.
好好跟你妈去放松下吧
Go have fun with your mom.
- 好吧    - 差点忘了 我带了东西给你
- Okay.   - Almost forgot. I got you something.
Lieutenant Kali, 我们之前谈到过的那个街头艺术家
It's Lieutenant Kali,
the street artist we talked about.
我让他给你画了这个 "童话故事"
I got him to do something for you.
"F-tale." Fairytale.
- 我知道你很喜欢这种小女孩玩意 所以..
- 这真酷啊
- I know you're into that girly shit, so...
- This is so cool.
Dylan 你真是太贴心了
Dylan, that's actually really sweet.
- 很酷是吧            - 是啊 谢谢你
- It's cool, right?   - Yeah. Thank you.
我得找你借钱打车回去了
Hey, I'm gonna need to borrow cab fare.
我可不想带着它去挤地铁 不想弄坏它
I'm not taking that thing on the subway.
I don't wanna get rolled.
没问题
No problem.
只要你把脚从我床上拿开就行 真是恶心
As long as you get your feet off my bed.
They're disgusting.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
你干嘛呢 干嘛呢
Why are you doing that?
别这么蛮横好吗 别搞了!
You're an animal. Stop doing that.
An animal. Stop.
嘿 妈
Hey, Ma.
妈 来啊 我们得出发了
Ma. Come on, we gotta get on the road.
妈
Come on.
Ma?
Jamie 抱歉 我去找我的前未婚夫了
怎么我感觉这一次跟以前不一样
Why did I think that
this time would be any different?
- 跟我去洛杉矶         - 什么?
- Come with me to LA.  - What?
你还能干什么 国庆节啊 所有人都出去玩了
What else are you gonna do?
It's 4th of July, everybody's left the city.
谢谢你的邀请 但我没事
You're very sweet for
asking, but it's fine.
我就待在家 我一个人待着没事的
You know what, I'll just stay here.
I'll be fine alone.
我知道你一个人待着没事 你又不是锁在车里的婴儿
I know you'll be fine alone.
You're not a baby in a hot car.
我想你来是因为或许你能帮到我
I'm actually asking you to come
because it would help me.
你能把我家人吸引开来
You'd be a great distraction for my family.
他们就不会因为我还是单身而念叨了
They'd forget all about
drilling me for being single.
他们不会觉得我们是一对吗
Won't they think that we're together?
- 我跟他们说就行了
- 他们会相信?
- Not if I tell them we're not.
- And they'll believe you?
我们家里从来都是很坦诚的
Yeah, we're one of these crazy families
that doesn't lie to each other.
电视台都为我们家拍纪录片呢
PBS is doing a documentary on us.
来吧 他们会喜欢你的
Come on, they'll love you.
说话又快又直接 就跟我带个演员回家一样
All fast-talking and brusque,
like I'm bringing home a carny.
感谢你的邀请 但我还是在家待着好了
You're really nice to ask,
but I'm just gonna stay here.
我会去健身房
Go to the gym.
票都帮你买好了 我在机场等你
I just got you a ticket with my miles,
it's done. Meet me at JFK.
- 但是..  - 没有但是
- But...  - No buts.
- 就像去健身房一样                    - 但那不是啊
- Like you were gonna go to the gym. - I wasn't.
洛杉矶可好玩了
LA's so nice.
所有人都很和气真诚
And everyone's so genuine and level-headed.
谢谢 你真好
Thanks for this. You're good peeps.
你也不赖啊
You're the good peeps, dude.
你还没见过我家人 你还不知道呢
You haven't met my family.
You don't know what you're in for.
好吧
Okay.
你知道飞机都是自己降落的吗
You know these planes
pretty much land themselves?
谁管它呢 别扯淡
Nobody cares. You sound like an asshole.
纽约来的
She's from New York.
对不起
I'm sorry.
哇 看起来不错啊
Wow. This looks normal.
是啊
It is.
谢谢
Thank you.
哇 你在这儿长大?
Wow, you grew up here?
这是我爷爷家的房子
It was my grandfather's.
这里什么都没有的时候他就买下了这里
He bought it
when there was nothing else here.
我爸爸 姐姐 还有我侄儿住在这里
My dad and my sister
and her son live here now.
那你为什么你要去纽约啊
Why would you move to New York?
被某个猎头骗去的
I was conned by some headhunter.
- 你来了         - Sammy!
- You're here.  - Sammy!
嘿 Dylan叔叔
Hey, Uncle Dylan.
最近怎么样 小家伙
What's up, buddy?
最近可好
How are you?
Jamie 这是我的侄子 Sam
Jamie, this is my nephew,
Sam the Magnificent.
- 你好
- 要我为你点烟吗?
- Hello.
- May I offer you a light for your cigarette?
抱歉 我不抽烟
I'm sorry, I don't smoke.
装个样子 他会魔术
Just pretend. He's a magician.
当然我抽烟了 吸烟有益健康
Of course I'll have a cigarette.
Smoking is great for you.
- 哇 谢谢 好先生              - 我的荣幸 我的女士
- Wow. Thank you, good sir.   - My pleasure, my lady.
天哪 没事了 没事了
Oh, my God. I got it, I got it.
Sammy 没事了 没事了 别动 没事了
Sammy. I got it, I got it.
Just stay still. I got it, I got it.
Sammy! 你没事吧?
Sammy! Are you okay?
这也是幻觉表演的一部分
All part of the illusion.
- 等会骑水上摩托去?     - 好呀
- Jet Skis later?      - Definitely.
还是着迷于魔术是吧?
Still into magic, huh?
是啊 他还喜欢给他的朋友发色情短信呢
Yep. But I'll take that over him
sexting his friends any day.
- Dilbert!  - Banannie
- Dilbert!  - Banannie.
Jamie 这是我姐姐Annie
Jamie, this is my sister, Annie.
- 你好    - 谢谢你的招待
- Hi.     - Thank you for having me.
噢 别客气 很高兴Dylan能带女孩回家
Oh, please.
It's nice to have Dylan bring a girl home.
- 我们只是普通朋友       - 噢 我知道
- We're just friends.   - Oh, no, I know.
你要是是他的女朋友 他才不会带你来呢
If you were his girlfriend,
he never would've brought you here.
- 他有亲密感障碍                  - 我知道
- This one has intimacy issues.   - I know.
- Dylan   - 爸
- Dylan.  - Dad.
- 噢 Dylan           - 嘿
- Dylan. Oh, man.    - Hey.
- 最近怎么样 伙计         - 很好
- How you doing, buddy?   - I'm good.
除了很想你们大家
I miss you guys, but I'm good.
Dede Spencer?
我是Jamie   Dylan的朋友
Jamie. Dylan's friend.
- 抱歉 我..         - 没事
- I'm sorry. I...    - That's okay.
刚才你让我想起了一个以前认识的女孩
No, for a minute you reminded me
of a girl I used to know.
- 没 没事 常有的事嘛            - 很高兴见到你
- No, that's okay. It happens.  - Nice to meet you.
认识你很荣幸 你们家真漂亮
Pleasure meeting you.
You have a beautiful house.
谢谢
Thank you.
游泳池里水有点凉 因为加温太耗钱..所以
Pool's a little cold,
but it's very expensive to heat, so...
我得去看下潮汐监测表
I think I'm gonna goin
and check the tide tables
因为我想早上去驾船航行
'cause I'm gonna take the boat out
early in the morning.
- 你应该一起来        - 我很乐意
- You should come.   - I would love to.
船已经卖掉了
We sold the boat.
医生不想让你继续开船了
The doctor doesn't want you
driving the boat any more.
- 脑子秀逗了
- Turning to mush.
见到你真好
It's good to see you, buddy.
- 见到你真好        - 我也是
- Nice to meet you.  - It was nice meeting you, too.
- Jamie 没错吧?    - 是的
- Jamie. See?      - Yes.
- 裤子呢?                  - 他已经不喜欢穿裤子了
- What's with the pants?   - He doesn't like them any more.
越来越糟糕了
He's getting worse.
很高兴你们能来
It's so good to have you here.
带她去海滩啊
Go show her the beach.
- 来 我们去海滩                        - 好啊
- Let me show you the beach. Come on.  - Okay.
- 尽情的玩沙吧                        - 好
- Go, get sandy. Get all messed up.  - Okay.
Dylan从未跟我谈起过他的父亲
Dylan never told me about your dad.
是啊 对他来说很艰难 他们曾经很亲密
Yeah, it's been tough on him.
They were real close.
Dylan不怎么知道去适应老年痴呆的人
Dylan doesn't quite know
how to deal with the Alzheimer's.
很遗憾
I'm sorry.
他可以跟原来一样 看起来一切都好
He'll be his regular old self
and everything seems fine,
但是眨眼之间 也许就会离我们而去
and then just in a flash, he's gone.
- 那是Dylan九岁的时候              - 那是鞭子吗
- That's Dylan when he was nine.  - Are those braids?
他是Kris Kross的粉丝 记得他们吗?
He was going through a Kris Kross phase.
Remember them?
- 那是你母亲吗?     - 不是 那是Dylan的语言治疗师
- Is that your mom? - No, that's Dylan's speech therapist.
他有口吃 特别是他一紧张就越严重
He had a stutter.
It got real bad when he was nervous.
他的童年过得很艰难
He had a rough childhood.
- 他的数学家教管这叫" 陶冶情操"
- 数学家教?
- His math tutor called it "character-building."
- Math tutor?
我们讨论的是 8*6=1200
No, we're talking, like,
8 times 6 equals 1,200.
感谢上帝他至少长的帅
But he's very visual, thank God.
- 能说说这张相片吗
- 那是我的12岁惊喜生日派对
- Can you please explain to me this photo?
- That is my 12th-birthday surprise party.
- 嘿       - 美妙的时刻
- Hey.    - Amazing moment.
我很累 我去睡觉了
I'm exhausted. I'm gonna go to bed.
- Jamie 房间觉得怎么样
- 很完美
- Jamie, you all good with your room?
- Yeah. No, it's perfect.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you for everything.
Sam和我做了把女孩切成两半的魔术盒 所以你回房间的时候要小心
Sammy and I built a saw-a-girl-in-half box,
so just be careful on your way to bed.
- 他不是真的用锯子吧?
- 当然是
- He's not using a real saw, is he?
- Of course he is. He's magnificent.
我会确保他有刷牙 还有你 别相信她说的
I'll make sure he brushes his teeth,
and you, don't believe anything she says.
她是个骗子
She's a liar.
- 他很特别                    - 是啊
- He's a pretty special guy.  - Yeah, I think so.
- Jamie           - 嘿
- Jamie. Hey.   - Hey.
- 没睡吧?    - 是啊
- You up?   - Yeah. Come in.
- 我以为你去睡觉了呢                 - 是啊
- I thought you were going to bed.  - I was.
但是我意识到我们又都回到了单身 所以...
But then I realized
we were both single again, so...
- 不了 老兄    - 为什么
- Dude, no.   - Why not?
这次我用香皂洗过手了
I washed my hands. With soap this time.
你认真的? 你怎么以为我有那个意思
Are you serious?
Why would you just assume?
你在阳台上扭了扭脖子 这动作.. 就是信号 记得吗
You cracked your neck on the porch.
This thing. That's your tell, remember?
我扭一扭脖子是因为我们坐了六个小时飞机
I cracked my neck
because we were on a flight for six hours,
你一直在我耳边念叨飞机是怎么飞的
and you were yapping my ear off
about how planes all fly themselves,
我脖子都要抽筋了
and it actually kinked my neck a bit.
- 所以 你不想喽?      - 不想 不想和你上床
- So, no?            -No. Not having sex with you.
大姨妈来了?  他们做了个软件 等等
Is it your special time?
They have an app for that. No, wait.
- 没来 你现在是安全期        - 我们谈过了
- Nope, you're good to go.  - We talked about this.
- 再说 我刚被甩 所以                  - 好吧 对不起
- Plus, I just got dumped, so...     - Okay, I'm sorry.
我以为这样能帮你忘掉他
I thought this would be a good way
to take your mind off him.
不 上床治不好我的情伤
No, I don't function that way.
Sex is not gonna help.
你知道什么能治好我吗  情感
But you know what will? Emotional support.
之前我们有性无爱 现在我们却有爱无性
Before we were sex without emotion,
and now we're emotion without sex.
正是
Exactly.
我现在只想你做我的朋友
I just need you to be my friend right now.
好吧 那我就听你说话 然后你一边帮我打飞机吧
Okay. So I'll listen to you
while you give me a hand job.
- 不要        - 开玩笑  我知道了  晚安
- No.         - I'm kidding. I got it. Good night.
等等 朋友也可以待在一起 听听音乐什么的嘛
Wait, hold on! Friends can still hang out
and, I don't know, listen to music.
听音乐?
Listen to music?
我要杀了Annie
I'm gonna kill Annie.
- 真不敢相信你以前很喜欢他们
- 我不喜欢他们
- I can't believe you used to like them.
- I didn't like these guys.
我甚至都不记得
I don't even remember...
你开玩笑呢 这些家伙很带感的
Are you kidding me?
These dudes were da bomb.
大家都反戴着Girbauds的帽子
Everybody had Girbauds,
we all wore them backwards.
穿着棒球衫
The baseball jerseys.
连续3年万圣节 我都打扮成Kris Kross
I went as Kris Kross
three years in a row for Halloween.
- 噢 可怜的小孩       - 我可并不为此骄傲
- Oh, you poor kid.  - I'm not proud of it.
嘿 我借了你一本书 希望你不介意
Hey, I borrowed one of your books.
I hope that's okay.
吓死你!
Surprise!
你以前真的没有带女孩回家过吗
Have you really never brought
a girl home before?
我带你来了
I brought you here.
我意思是女朋友 不是女性朋友
I mean like a real girl. Not a friend.
- 女朋友?         - 是啊
- A real girl?   - Yeah.
我想没有
I guess not.
- 我分得很清楚                       - 啊 是啊
- Separation of church and state.   - Ah, yes.
筑起一道又一道心墙 太有益健康了
Build up as many walls as possible.
That's really healthy.
- 什么 你要跟我谈这个?                      - 是啊
- What, are you talking to me about walls?  - Yeah.
你和你母亲又怎么了
What about you and your mom?
你不能她一刚进门就把我赶出去啊
You couldn't get me out of there fast
enough when she walked in on us.
那是为了保护你 懂吗
That was for your own protection. Okay?
她没给你留电话我已经很惊讶了
I'm just surprised she didn't try
to slip you her number or something.
她留了 在我手机上
She did. She put it in my phone.
- 还取名"御姐"    - 噢 天哪
- Under "MILF."   - Oh, my God.
很好啊 我们就勾搭过一两次
It's cool, we only hooked up, like, twice.
我脑子里已经快出现那个画面了
I'm starting to get a mental image.
我还有个视频
Well, I have a video image.
别 住手
No. Just stop it. Just stop it.
这是错误的
Just wrong.
什么?
What?
没什么 很高兴遇到了你
Nothing. Just glad I met you.
是啊 遇到你也不是太糟糕哈
Yeah, well, knowing you
doesn't suck either.
- 我以为你说....              - 我知道
- But I thought you said...  - I know what I said.
天哪
God.
Lasorda是个不错的投手 但更是个好经理人
Lasorda was a good pitcher,
but he was an even better manager.
- 营救小组?
- 我没说他不是一名伟大的经理人
- Wrecking Crew?
- I wasn't saying he's not a great manager.
我只想说 他作为投手并为受到足够的赏识
He's underappreciated as a pitcher,
that's all I'm saying.
我们懂
We get it. Guys.
- 嗨    - 早上好
- Hi.   - Morning.
- 早上好          - 这总是这么美丽吗
- Good morning.  - Is it always this beautiful out here?
火灾洪灾之间 我们大概有10天好日子
Well, in between the fires and the floods,
we get about 10 good days.
来 你俩坐一起
No, no. Here. You two sit together.
- 确定吗            - 是的 是的
- Are you sure?    - Oh, yeah, no, no.
- 没必要这样 老爸
- 我知道 我只是想看看船
- You don't have to do that, Dad.
- I know. I wanna look at the boat.
我喜欢那船
I love that boat.
- 不好意思       - 很好 谢谢
- Here. Sorry.  - Great. Thanks.
谢谢  好了
Thank you. This... Okay.
- 咖啡? 我的女士      - 好 谢谢
- Coffee, my lady?   - Yes, please.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 不错啊 伙计!        - 真厉害
- All right, man!    - Look at you!
- 真令人大开眼界              - 耶 小Sam
- That's pretty impressive.  - Yay, Sammy!
好了!
All right!
呃..你的衬衫都漏水了 这...
Oh, buddy. Your shirt's leaking.
Oh, no, that's...
抱歉
Apologies.
- 你还好吗?     - 恩
- You okay?    - Yeah.
- 你呢      - 很好
- You?      - Yeah.
- 看到了吗 小Sam      - 是啊
- See them, Sammy?    - Yeah.
- 真酷 对吧             - 恩
- Pretty cool, huh?     - Yeah.
上帝啊 真棒
God, it's nice.
我真怀念这的早餐 艳阳高照之前 这真的美极了
I do miss the mornings out here.
Right before it burns off, it really is beautiful.
我喜欢Jamie
I like Jamie.
她也很漂亮
And she's pretty, too.
嘿 别乱来 别在她身上施什么法术
Hey, easy, dude.
Don't you go casting a spell on her.
我是魔术师 不是巫师 你这哈利波特基友
I'm a magician, not a wizard.
You and your gay Harry Potter.
去了霍格沃茨学院改变了你的人生
You can't deny that going to Hogwarts
wouldn't be life-changing.
- 我想你        - 我也想你
- I miss you.   - I miss you, too, bud.
妈妈也想你 爷爷也是
Mom misses you. And so does Grandpa.
他说什么了吗
Does he say anything?
没有 但他时常叫我Dylan
No. But sometimes he calls me Dylan.
他说过他不想要那份工作的
He said that he didn't want the job.
他去纽约只是为了看看有些什么选择
That he was just coming to New York
to explore his options.
胡说八道
What a crock of gas.
西海岸飞到东海岸就是为了看看有什么选择?
You fly across the country
to explore your options?
拜托 我可不觉得是那样
Please. I don't think so.
就是 自从他下飞机 我就知道我已经抓牢他了
Exactly! Please, I knew I had him
the second he got off that plane.
- 噢 是吗             - 是的
- Oh, did you, now?  - Yeah.
就是你光脚跳上行李传送带的那一刻?
Was that the same second you leapt
onto the baggage carousel barefoot
跟>里出现的那一幕一样?
and acted out a scene from Will and Grace?
- 她真那样?   - 噢 是啊 你真该看到的
- She did?   - Oh, yeah, you should have seen her.
"看着我 傻傻又可爱"
"Look at me, I'm goofy but cute."
你知道吗 那是我计划的一部分
You know what? It was all part of my plan.
好计划
Quite a plan.
猎头大学计划专业毕业的?
Did you major in Planning
at Headhunting College?
- 真聪明
- 那不是真的大学 侄子
- So clever.
- It's not a real college, by the way, buddy.
你们俩拌起嘴来就跟老夫老妻一样
You guys bicker like
you're an old married couple.
来 我的女士 选一张牌
Here, pick a card, my lady.
好的
Okay.
噢 别选那张 选上面这张
Oh, no, not that one. The one on top.
- 这把戏不错哦        - 所以
- This is a good one. - So...
- 恩?     - 洗牌
- Yeah?   - Shuffle.
你给她定情礼物了吗?
Did you get her an engagement gift?
我们没订婚 没在一起 只是朋友而已
We're not engaged, Dad. We're not together.
We're just friends.
好吧 你不想下定论 我理解 但至少送点珠宝吧
All right, you don't wanna label it.
I understand. But get her some jewelry.
你妈妈就最爱珠宝了
The only thing your mom loves is jewelry.
不管她多么的不开心 我送她珠宝 她立马就高兴起来
I don't care how upset she is,
I get her jewelry, she lights right up.
她在哪?
Where is she, anyway?
- 她没在这 爸爸
- 我知道 所以我才问你她在哪
- She's not here, Dad.
- I know, that's why I asked. Where is she?
- 她不会来            - 为什么?
- She's not coming.    - Why not?
她不再和你一起生活了 老爸
She doesn't live with you any more, Pop.
You're not married.
- 什么?    - 10年前她离开你了
- What?    - She left about 10 years ago.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你们离婚了 爸爸
She divorced you, Dad.
- 我得打电话给他         - 爸 你不能
- I have to call her.   - Dad, you can't.
别再指挥我该做什么
Stop telling me what to do.
爷爷
Grandpa!
- 没事吧 爸?        - 我没事
- You okay, Dad?   - I'm fine, I'm fine.
- 来 我扶你起来                - 不 不用你扶
- Here, let me help you up.   - No, don't. Don't!
我们到了
Here we are.
真美!
This is beautiful.
恩 我以前常来这思考问题 我的天台
Yeah, this is where I used to
come to think. My rooftop.
你觉得那栅栏有多高?
Okay, how high do you think that fence is?
我6英尺高多一点
I'm a little over 6 foot.
栅栏看起来有3个我这么高 所以6乘以3
Looks like it's about three of me.
So six times three...
就是92英尺了
Ninety-two feet.
- 92英尺! 真高呀 是吧                         - 是啊
- Ninety-two feet. That's really tall, right?  - Yeah.
他们不想让人上来这 所以才修了栅栏
But they don't want you to get up there,
so I guess that makes sense.
- 等等 6乘以3....            - 噢 上帝 可怜的孩子
- Wait. Six times three...  - Oh, God, you poor kid.
- 怎么了?      - 走吧
- What's up?   - Come on.
什么? 你要去哪啊?
What? What? Where are you going?
Jamie 别  等等  这事很严重的
Jamie, no, no, no, no, no, wait.
They take this shit seriously, okay?
看这些监控摄像头
Look at all the cameras.
这是除了山达基教中心外 这座城市的唯一地标了
This is the only landmark this city has
other than the Scientology Center.
如果这些摄像头跟山达基教中心联接起来
And if any of these cameras are hooked up
to the actual Scientology Center,
我很抱歉 这个笑话不妥
that was an inappropriate joke
and I apologize.
科幻小说万岁!
I believe in the freedom
of science fiction.
胆小鬼 ..不好意思
Pussy! Oh, sorry.
胆小鬼
Pussy!
走吧!
Come on!
- 你真的从没来过这上面                    -没
- You really never been up here before    - No.
我也从没吸过毒
I've also never transferred
heroin in my rectum,
因为那是犯法的
'cause it's against the law.
你知道吗 有时候回答问题一个词就够
You know, sometimes a simple
yes or no answer is adequate.
嘿 为什么你从不跟我谈起你母亲
Hey, why didn't you tell me about your mom?
她不值得我谈
She's not worth talking about.
这样说不太好吧
That's rough.
抛弃家庭难道就好
So is leaving your husband and kids.
你也没跟我谈起过你父亲
Yeah, you never told me about him either.
知道吗 还有很多事你没告诉过我
You know, there's a lot of stuff
you didn't tell me.
我不想你可怜我
I don't want your pity.
我就是受不了人们同情的眼神
I can handle anything except
that look in people's eyes.
- 就那样      - 谁在意啊
- That one.  - Who cares what anybody thinks?
他是我认识的最聪明的人 我只听取他的建议
He's the smartest man I've ever known.
He's the only person I'd ever go to for advice.
他是我父亲
He's my dad.
Dylan 他还是他
Dylan, he's still the same man.
当我看到人们看着他的那种眼神
When I see the way people
look at him now...
别人的眼光不重要啊
It doesn't matter how people look at him.
只有你的眼神才是最重要的
All that matters is how you look at him.
是啊 但人们都看着他没穿裤子到处晃悠
Yeah, but he's walking around
without his pants. Everyone's staring.
- 那又怎样?       - 很尴尬
- So what?        - It's embarrassing.
他需要知道什么都没改变
He needs to know that nothing has changed.
对你来说 他还是那个他
That he's still that same man to you.
我们能换个话题吗
Can we stop talking about this?
好吧 真聪明 别谈什么感受了
Yeah, that's really smart.
Let's just not talk about our feelings.
我尽量不去
I'm trying not to.
行了 有什么不对劲吗? 你最近有点奇怪
Come on. Is something going on here?
You've been acting really weird.
- 没啊            - 你有
- No, I haven't.  - Yeah, you have.
是不是关于那天晚上发生的事?
Is this about what
happened the other night?
什么事? 上床? 那不代表什么 你知道的
What, sex? That doesn't mean anything.
You know that.
是啊
Right.
- 我也没有变得古怪                   - 好吧
- And I haven't been acting weird.   - Okay.
- 噢 上帝啊    - 噢 靠
- Oh, my God! - Oh, shit!
- 跟你说了!      - 好吧 对不起!
- I told you!   - Well, I'm sorry!
我擦!
Fuck!
这是洛杉矶警察局,你涉嫌非法侵入 从标牌上下来
This is the LAPD. You are trespassing.
Get down from the sign.
我们得跳下去
We gotta jump.
- Dylan 跳啊!    - 我动不了了
- Dylan, jump!   - I'm frozen.
快下来啊
Come on, get down!
最后警告一次
Sin this is your last warning.
- 用楼梯啊            - 我有恐高症
- Use the ladder!     - I have a fear of heights!
我也怕直升机!
And also helicopters!
They don't make sense to me!
你说你有恐高症是什么意思?
What do you mean
you have a fear of heights?
那你为什么还要上来
Why would you come up here?
你骂我胆小鬼
You called me a pussy!
今天下午 在南部发生了一件奇闻趣事
A bizarre situation
this afternoon in the Southland.
洛杉矶警察局从城市的唯一地标:好莱坞山顶字牌上
The LAPD rescued a local man from the Hollywood sign
解救了一位当地民众
the city's only real landmark.
他们居然把你包在毯子里
They actually wrapped
you in a foil blanket!
你之前是去跑马拉松了吗?
Did you run a marathon before this?
- 好了 给我          - 不
- Okay. Give me...  - No!
- 不 我想录下来 我得录下来
- 住手 够了!
- No, no. I wanna save it. I gotta save it.
- No. That's enough!
- 给我遥控器! 闭嘴 - 我要一遍又一遍的看
- Give me the remote! Shut up!
- No, I wanna watch it over and over.
大毛毯
Foil wrapper...
好了 好了 好了
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
会上Youtube的
It's okay, it'll be up on YouTube.
嘿 我带Sam去特区的时候 你能帮我照看下老爸吧?
Hey, you're still good to take Dad that week I
have to go to DC for Sam's class trip, right?
- 恩 他在纽约跟我待一起                        - 恩 那好
- Yeah, he's gonna stay with me in New York.  - Oh, good.
那 我们时候能再见到Jamie?
So, when are we gonna see Jamie again?
我不知道
I don't know.
怎么了  跟她吵架了?
What's your problem?
Did you have a fight with your girlfriend?
她不是我女朋友 你就怎么不相信呢
She's not my girlfriend.
Why don't you believe me?
你要是诚实点 我就信了
I would believe you if
you didn't lie to me.
那天晚上我看见你从她房间蹑手蹑脚的溜出来
I saw you creeping out of her room
the other night.
就像刚做完爱从床上下来 懂我意思吧
Like you had just had sex,
if you know what I mean.
我懂你刚说的
Yes, I know what you
mean, you just said it.
你怎么知道我跟她做...
And how do you know
what I look like after I have...
我才不和你谈这个呢 又不是我们谈恋爱
I'm not talking to you about this, okay?
We're not together.
- Dylan     - 够了! 我不想谈这个了
- Dylan.    - Enough! I'm not talking about it.
Dylan
Dylan.
忘记拿锯子了 马上回来
Forgot my saw. I'll be right back.
我等你 别担心我
I'll wait here. Don't worry about me.
普通朋友也上床?  你以为是大学里啊?
Friends who have sex?
What are you, in college?
- 不重要了 结束了                - 为什么?
- It doesn't matter, it's over.   - Why?
因为我们不是真心实意喜欢对方的
Because we don't like each other like that.
好吧 我们坐下来谈谈
Okay, you know what?
Can we just talk about this? Sit down.
你还在寻找什么
What more are you looking for?
- 谁说我还在寻找?                      - Dylan
- Who says I'm looking for anything?  - Dylan.
- 我不知道 但我要的不是Jamie
- 为什么 因为你们很合拍?
- I don't know, but it's not Jamie.
- Why, because you're great together?
因为你们是好朋友?
Because you're actually
friends with each other?
因为这是我见过的最快乐的你?
Because this is the happiest
I have ever seen you?
我不知道该说些什么 反正她不适合我 我不喜欢真心喜欢她
I don't know what to tell you. She's not for me.
I don't like her like that.
- 你足够喜欢她 所以才和她上床
- 只是生理需求而已
- You liked her enough to have sex with her.
- It's just physical.
- 就像打网球
- 我搞不懂你这套网球理论 Dylan
- Like playing tennis.
- I don't even know what that means, Dylan.
自从你弄了那个玉米糖纹身之后我就没见你这么傻过了
I haven't seen you this dumb
since you got that candy corn tattoo.
那是闪电! 超能力
It's a lightning bolt! With extra powers!
Dylan 你都说不出她有什么不好的地方
Dylan, you can't name
one thing that's wrong with her.
我不可能跟她约会 她真是一团糟
I can never go out with her.
She's too fucked up.
她不需要男朋友
Okay, she doesn't want a boyfriend.
她情感很受伤
She's too damaged.
夏威夷神探都解决不了她的问题
Magnum P.l. couldn't solve
the shit going on in her head.
哇 你说了一大堆 却都不承认
Wow. You'll say anything right now
你们其实是天生一对
not to admit that
you're perfect for each other.
- 为什么我还要跟你聊这个话题
- 因为我是对的
- Why am I still having this conversation?
- Because I'm right.
- 说得真好 Annie     - Dylan
- Good talk, Annie.  - Dylan.
- 科比太神奇了!
- Kobe Bryant is incredible.
- 男人啊 就是钟情于体育
- You're men. You like sports. You're men.
嘿 我们正等你呢
Hey! We were waiting for you.
我刚接到了纽约那边的电话
I actually got a call from work.
今晚得搭红眼航班回纽约了
I have to be on a red eye tonight
back to New York.
- 今晚?     - 是啊
- Tonight?  - Yeah.
- 明天就是国庆日啊       - 是啊 很恶心
- Tomorrow's the 4th.   - I know, it sucks.
那好吧 那我至少送你去机场
Well, at least let me
drive you to the airport.
不用了 谢谢 我已经叫了出租车了 就在门外
No, no. It's fine. Stay.
I already called a cab. It's out front.
谢谢你们大家
But thank you guys for everything.
谢谢你们让我住在这儿 感觉很棒
And thank you for letting me stay here.
It's been pretty great.
- 嘿     - 嘿
- Hey.   - Hey.
- 没事吧?                  - 没事 很好啊
- Everything okay, buddy? - Yeah, buddy. Everything's great.
我真得走了
I just really gotta go.
那 再次感谢 我真的得走了
So, thank you again. I'm sorry I gotta go.
- 让Dylan送你去         - 恩
- Let Dylan drive you.  - Yeah.
- 路上带点东西吃吗?
- 我把你一分为二怎么样?
- Do you wanna take some food to go?
- Do you want me to saw you in half?
下半身去纽约工作 上半身继续留在这
You can send your bottom part to New York
and your top half can stay here.
或者你就干脆留下
Or the whole of you could stay.
行了 对不起 我得走了
Okay, I'm sorry. I gotta go.
Jamie
Jamie!
她走了 上了辆出租车
She's gone. She hopped in the cab.
- 我们吃饭吧 饿了吧?                   - 是啊
- We should eat. You hungry, buddy?   - Yeah.
盘子拿给我
Okay. Hand me your plate.
嘿 老兄 你饿吗? 我正要去弄点吃的
Hey, bro. You hungry?
'Cause I'm going to get something to eat.
谢了 我还是不吃午餐继续工作了
Thanks, man.
I think I'm just gonna work through lunch.
岗位道德 我喜欢 这就是为什么这个国家还是世界第一
A work ethic. I love it.
That is why this country is still number one.
好吧 排在德国法国比利时日本中国等等之后...
Well, behind Germany and France
and Belgium and Japan and China and...
感谢上帝我们排在孟加拉前面
Thank God for Bangladesh.
顺便问一下 你干嘛要把门拆下来啊
By the way, why did you take
your door off its lovely hinges?
这很蠢啊 老兄 我从管理学的书上看到的
It was dumb, man.
Something I saw in a management book.
噢 好吧 这就是巴菲特是怎么发财的
Oh, right, right.
Like, that's how Warren Buffett got rich.
他把门都拆了
He took doors off of things.
嘿 人人都想要一条生活的捷径
Hey, everybody wants a shortcut in life.
我的手册很简单 想减肥?
My guidebook is very simple.
You wanna lose weight?
别吃高脂肪食物
Stop eating, fatty.
想赚钱?
You wanna make money?
拼命工作吧 懒鬼
Work your ass off, lazy.
你想快乐?
You wanna be happy?
找个你喜欢的人 怎么都别开他的放手
Find someone you like and never let him go.
或者说她的手 如果你起了鸡皮疙瘩的话
Or her, if you're into
that Kind of creepy shit.
你好 这是Jamie Rellis的电话 我现在不方便接电话
Hi, you've reached Jamie Rellis.
I can't pick up the phone right now
请留言 我会打回给你
but please leave a message
and I'll call you back.
妈 你得对着屏幕啊 不然它怎么知道你在哪
Mom, Mom, you gotta point it at the screen.
You gotta tell it where you are.
好吧 我不玩了 喝一杯去..
Fine. I'm over here pouring myself a drink.
邀性来电哦 我先去街角散个步
Booty call.
I can take a walk around the block.
不 妈 没事
No, no. Nope, that's okay.
这是你的公寓 我可不想打扰你的性致
This is your apartment.
I don't wanna twat-block you.
是Dylan?
That's Dylan, right?
- 他看起来蛮不错的          - 你就见过他一次
- He seemed pretty great.  - You met him once.
比起其他男友 这已经足够好了
Well, that's more than
anybody else you've dated.
不知道 你以为我发神经没事去躲着他?
I don't know, you think maybe I keep
my worlds apart for some crazy reason?
我真是个混蛋
I am an asshole.
我们正在寻找一个能带领重新设计我们网站的人
We're looking for someone
to lead the redesign of our entire website.
一个能使我们网站焕然一新的人
Someone to turn it completely upside down.
你不能告诉我你为哪个公司工作?
But you can't tell me
what company you work for?
为了保密 不能
For confidentiality reasons, no.
给个提示?
Can you give me a hint?
我们可能是网上最大的零售商
We may or may not be the largest seller
of purchased goods on the Internet.
零售商品指的是书籍
And by 'purchased goods, ” I mean books.
你刚为GQ杂志物色到一个艺术总监 对吧
You just placed the new art director
over at GQ, right?
是啊
Yeah.
我们要的就是那种类型的人 呃 我们要的就是那个人
That's the type of guy we want.
Shoot, that's the guy we want.
你能把他挖过来我们这边吗?
Can you get him to come out to us?
我跟他已经没有关系了
No longer have a relationship with him.
- 你能找到他吗?
- 他还处于合同的第一年呢
- Can you get to him?
- He's still in the first year of his contract,
所以那不太合适吧
so that would be inappropriate.
那有什么不合适的
So is paying full price
for a book at Barnes & Noble,but people do dumb shit.
你好 这是Jamie Rellis的电话 我不方便接电话
Hi, you've reached Jamie Rellis.
I can't pick up the phone right now
请留言 我会打回给你
but please leave a message
and I'll call you back.
哇 直接就进了语音信箱 响都没响一声
Wow, right to voice mail. Didn't even ring.
Jamie
Jamie.
你怎么知道我在这
How'd you know I was up here?
城市里唯一收不到手机信号的地方
Only place in the city
you don't get reception.
是啊
Right.
- 为什么要躲着我              - 我没有
- Why are you avoiding me?   - I'm not.
真的吗? 得了吧 Jamie
Really? Come on, Jamie.
Dylan 不知道你听说没有 我真是一团糟
Well, Dylan, I don't know if you've heard,
but I am seriously fucked up.
夏威夷神探都帮不了我
I mean, Magnum P.I. couldn't solve
the shit going on up here.
- 噢上帝 我很抱歉          -  我还是先去搞定我的一团糟
- Oh, my God, I'm sorry.   - But I'm just gonna go
如果还有可能的话
and try to fix the shit going on up
in my head, if that's even possible.
我不该说那话的 我只是想让我姐不再烦我
I shouldn't have said that.
I was just trying to get my sister off my back.
- 她以为我们彼此真心喜欢           - 是啊 我也这么以为的
- She thought we liked each other. - Yeah, me, too, Dylan.
我以为我们是好朋友
I thought we were friends.
但是朋友之间不该指指点点
But friends don't go
talking shit about each other,
这就证明了我们其实并非朋友
which must mean that you and I
were actually never friends.
- 你想要的不过就是为了跟我上床                  - 什么?
- That all you wanted was to get in my pants.  - What?
在你父亲家里 你抓住了机会
You jumped at the chance
at your dad's house.
你扭了脖子
You cracked your neck.
我以为那是信号 我们谈过的
I thought you were giving me a sign.
We talked about this.
噢 天哪 真的吗
Oh, my God, really?
你脱掉我的睡袍 记得吗
You pulled my robe off.
"Oopsy." Remember?
然后你偷偷摸摸出了房间
Yeah. And then you snuck out of the room.
记得吗
"Oopsy." Remember that?
你是为了我没搂着你睡觉而生气吗
Are you pissed off at me
because I didn't cuddle?
我们一开始不就是这么安排的吗
Isn't that why we started
this whole arrangement in the first place?
是你要这样的
You wanted this.
我?
I wanted this?
就我?
Just me?
上帝 原来你跟其他人也没什么两样
God, you are just like every other guy.
遗憾的是 我还以为你与众不同呢 Dylan
The sad thing is, Dylan,
I actually thought you were different.
有什么不同? 我又不是你男朋友 我只是普通朋友
Different from what?
I'm not your boyfriend, I'm your friend.
如果朋友都跟你一样 谁还需要朋友?
Well, with friends like you,
who needs friends?
谢谢你毁了我的宁静
And thank you for ruining my mountaintop.
王八蛋
Asshole.
嘿 老兄 你不能待在这上面
Hey, man, you can't be up here.
好的
Okay.
- 你没事吧    - 我很好
- You okay?   - I'm fine.
Bryce 这是给我的?
Bryce, is this for me?
是啊 还有这个
Yeah. And so is this.
Madison 你愿意嫁给我吗
Madison, will you marry me?
我愿意
You bet your ass, Flapjack!
- 我爱纽约           - 我爱你
- I love New York.   - I love you.
噢 天哪 看 帝国大厦
Oh, my God.
Look, the Empire State Building.
哇
Wow.
看 自由女神像
Oh, look, the Statue of Liberty.
你好 我是Jamie
Hello, this is Jamie.
什么意思 他们要直接跟他接触?
What do you mean they went to him directly?
他会接受吗
Well, is he gonna take it?
不 不 不 我能搞定 我马上给他打电话
No, no, no, no, no. I'll handle it.
I'll call him right now.
好吧
Okay.
嘿 这是Dylan 请留言
Hey this is Dylan. Leave a message.
我能帮你什么忙吗
Excuse me. May I help you?
你好 Dylan在哪?
Oh, hi. Where's Dylan Harper?
他在拍运动版封面
He's at a photo shoot for the sports issue.
是啊 拍封面 在哪拍?
That's right. The photo shoot.
Where was that again?
不好意思 你是谁?
I'm sorry. Who are you?
一个模特
One of the models.
我的身体很完美
I have the perfect body for Photoshop.
五官玲珑有致 身材修长
Yeah, this gets more angular,
these get longer,
很有基督徒气质
and this gets way more Christian.
所以 他在哪?
So where did you say he was again?
体育运动是连接这个世界的最后一根纽带 老兄
Sports is the last chance we have
of bringing our world together, bro.
所以我想拍一些照片
So I just wanted to shoot some photos
that speak to that,
来让所有人类都为体育运动而团结一心
to the unification of all people
through sports.
好了 大家伙 我们开始
Okay, guys. Let's go.
就是那样
That's it.
漂亮
Beautiful.
好的 现在请大家肩并肩
Okay, now put your arms around each other,
就像喜欢对方一样
like you like each other,
like you love each other.
- 太基了?     - 有点
- Too gay?   - A little bit.
放几个女孩子进去
Throw some girls in there.
去吧 女孩们
Come on, ladies. Hop to.
女孩们 来吧 加入进去
Girls, girls. Okay, look. Just blend in.
好的 男生女生各就各位
Okay, let's go boy, girl, boy...
- Dylan
- Dylan.
- ...boy, boy, boy, boys.
- 你来这干嘛                - 你面试了另一份工作!
- What are you doing here? - You met for another job!
- 怎么 你想要跳槽?
- 我不知道 我去见了个面
- What, are you gonna leave now?
- I don't know. Yeah, I took one meeting.
- 难以置信               - 过来
- I can't believe you.  - Come here.
- 这是你复仇的方式吗?                        - 什么?
- Is this your way of getting back at me?   - What?
你知道如果一年未满你就走了 我就完了
You know that if you leave
before a year is up, I get screwed.
噢 是嘛
Oh, right.
如果我真的辞职
If I did leave,
还不确定 只是我只是去见了个面而已
which I don't know yet
because all I did was take one meeting,
我也会把奖金给你
I'd write you a check for your bonus.
不管怎样 我都会赔偿你的损失 高兴了吧? 没事了吧?
Whatever it is, I'll pay for it.
Happy now? We good?
- 为什么你不告诉我你去找新工作了
- 个人隐私
- Why didn't you tell me you were looking?
- That's personal.
何况我们已经不是朋友 你说得很清楚了
And we're not friends any more.
You made that pretty clear.
我只是想和你上床而已 记得吗
See, all I wanted to do
was have sex with you. Remember?
假装你是我最好的朋友
Pretend you were the best
friend I'd ever had.
假装从未对其他人那样 向你打开心扉
Open up to you
like I've never done with anyone ever.
然后我们没继续上床了 我邀请你到
And then when the sex stopped,
invite you to LA for the weekend
洛杉矶 向我的家人介绍你
to introduce you to my family.
- 拿到那份工作 我会给你寄支票的              - 不麻烦你了
- I'll send you a check if I take the job.  - Don't bother.
把他抬起来
Why don't you pick him up?
是的 抬起来
Yeah. Just pick him on up.
你真像个小救世主
Oh, you little Christ figure, you!
- 嘿
- 老爸会过来纽约吧?
- Hey, Dyl.
- Dad's coming into Newark Airport, right?
是啊 我们这边9点的时候他就出发
Yeah, he leaves at 9:00 our time.
9点.. 那就是5小时的飞机 3小时的时差
9:00. So it's a five-hour flight,
three-hour time difference,
所以他到这就是32点了
so he gets in at 32:00
是5点 记得5点到 Dylan
5:00. Be there at 5:00, Dylan.
对 爸爸怎么样
Right. How is Dad?
越来越糟糕了
He's lost more often than not now.
但有时候又思维很清晰 说不定的
But then he has these moments
of real clarity. It's hit or miss.
- 好吧    - Jamie如何
- Okay.   - How's Jamie?
- 已经结束了     - 噢 Dylan
- That's over.   - Oh, Dylan!
- 好了 别再说了       - 别犯傻啊
- Okay, we're done.   - Don't be an idiot, please.
谢谢 Annie 明天我会去机场接老爸的
Thank you, Annie.
I'll pick up Dad tomorrow at the airport.
- 32点准时       - 爱你
- 32:00 sharp.  - I love you.
我不知道到底怎么了
I don't know what it is.
我就是没办法重新振作起来
I just can't get myself
to start looking for a replacement for him,
再找一个替代他的人
assuming that he leaves.
- 你想要充满母爱的建议吗?
- 不想
- Do you want some motherly love advice?
- Not really.
太好了 因为也不知道怎么说
Oh, good, 'cause I don't know
how to do that.
我只知道现在你
What I do know is that
it's no great goddamn secret
就是怕会变得跟我一样
you live in fear of repeating my mistakes.
如果我没做错的话 那就跟我学吧
And you're not wrong, so learn from me.
你知道在辈子我所认为的完美的男人有多少个吗
Do you know how many men in my life
I thought were really perfect?
- 80       - 1
- Eighty.  - One.
- 81?          - 就1个
- Eighty-one?  - One.
就是你老爸 我遇到过的最好的男人
It was your dad. Greatest man I ever met.
很明显啊 看看你自己
Obviously. Look at you.
多么聪明善良风趣积极
How smart you are, how great,
how funny, how driven.
透着隐约的中东气质
Your vaguely Middle Eastern beauty.
我很肯定这不是从我这遗传的
Sure as hell didn't all come from me.
好吧 但是说真的 妈
Okay, but, seriously, Mom,
你真的不记得我爸爸是哪里人吗
do you really not remember
where my dad's from?
或者说你不想说呢
Or is it like a coping mechanism?
- 都有吧             - 好吧
- A little of both.  - Okay.
只能说我很肯定他是欧亚混血
But I'm pretty sure he's Eurasian.
我的意思是 我们都会等到我们的白马王子
你只需要知道他现在在你身边 而不是他从哪里来啊
I mean, we all have our Prince Charming,
you just gotta know him when you see him.
妈 这可是白马王子啊 你当然得知道啊
Mom, it's Prince Charming.
You should just know.
得了 你的白马王子又不是驾着四轮马车来拯救你的
Well, your Prince Charming isn't coming
to rescue you in a horse and carriage.
你不想我想啊
That's not who you want.
我意思是 你在寻找一个伴侣
I mean, you're looking for a man
to be your partner.
一起生活的
To take on the world with.
你不能还活在老套的童话故事里 宝贝
You gotta update your fairytale, baby.
我的白马王子?
My Prince Charming?
你
You.
妈
Mom.
- 嘿      -  轮椅哈? 好像我是个残废似的
- Hey.    - A wheelchair. Like I'm an invalid.
- 飞行如何?             - 我饿了
- How was the flight?   - I'm hungry.
长途都不提供餐点了?
You know they don't serve food
in coach any more?
这些飞机都是自己飞的 知道吗
You'd think with these new planes,
they practically fly themselves,
把付给飞行员的钱拿来提供热的午餐啊
they could get rid of a pilot
and use his salary for a hot lunch.
- 我知道 我们这就去吃点东西                  - 上帝
- I know, right? Let's get you some food.   - God.
飞机都这么先进了
The engineering on these planes
is so advanced.
完全电脑控制的
Completely computerized.
- 就跟玩游戏一样                     - 是啊
- It's like playing a video game.   - Exactly.
上帝啊 我们等了多久了 真是荒谬
God. How long have we been waiting here?
It's ridiculous.
我马上就回
I'll be right back, okay?
不好意思 我们已经等了很久了
Excuse me. We've been waiting a while.
- Harper     - 是的 是的 有你的名字
- Harper.    - Yeah, I got you. I got you.
但我得按顺序来安排座位
I have to seat people
in the order they came.
完全理解 但是我老爸
I totally understand that,
but I'm with my dad
- 他状况不太好                      - 对不起
- and he's not in the best shape.  - I'm sorry.
能想想办法腾一张桌子出来吗
Is there no way we could,
like, squeeze a table?
抱歉 不行 我得按照名单来
No, I gotta go by the list. Sorry.
爸爸?
Dad?
Shit. Dad?
要一起吗?
You gonna join me?
当然
Absolutely.
很抱歉 先生 你不能这样..
Excuse me, sir.
I'm sorry, you cannot do this.
请来一份中号牛排
Could I get a steak, medium, please?
- 先生 我们这只有烤肉               - 我也来一份牛排
- Sir, this is the Daily Grill.    - Make that two.
Dede Dede!
Dede? Dede!
爸
Dad.
谁是Dede啊?
Who is Dede?
老天 在海军的时候我认识的一个女孩
Jesus. She's just a girl
that I met in the Navy.
她是
Was...
她是我的一生挚爱
She was the love of my life.
知道吧?
Okay?
怎么你没跟我说起过她
Why didn't you tell me about her before?
这不是能和孩子们谈的话题
This is not something
you discuss with your children.
况且 我有你和Annie 一生无憾了
And besides, I have you and Annie.
I have no regrets.
那现在告诉我吧
So tell me now.
她是我最爱的人
She was the love of my life.
当时我太蠢居然没意识到
And I was too stupid to realize it,
因为一些愚蠢的事我失去了她
and I lost her because of something
so dumb I don't even remember.
至今我还忘不了她
And I never really got over her.
我想这也可能是为什么你母亲会离开
And I think that may be
one of the reasons your mom left.
知道吗 我朋友以前常说我和Dede四目相对时
You know, my friends used to say that
when Dede and I looked at each other,
都能放出电来
it was electric.
但我却没珍惜她
And I let her go.
放开了她的手
I just let her go.
因为我太傲慢以至于不能告诉她我对她真正的感觉
Because I was too damn proud
to tell her how l really felt about her.
当我是你这么大的时候 我真希望我也能明白的一个道理
I'll tell you something that I wish
I knew when I was your age.
或许你已经听了N遍了 那就是"人生苦短"
And I know you've heard
a million times, "life is short."
他教会了我
But let me tell you something,
what this is teaching me
人生苦短 你不能浪费一分一秒
is that life is goddamn short
and you can't waste a minute of it.
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
我带回来洛杉矶的女孩 Jamie?
The girl I brought home to LA, Jamie?
- 是啊 你跟她怎么了?                - 我想我搞砸了
- Yeah, what's going on with her? - I think I messed it up.
- 修复它      - 她不愿意跟我说话了
- Fix it.    - She won't talk to me.
可能她至少还会听 总有办法的
Maybe she'll listen. There's always a way.
如果你觉得她还有机会成为你的一生挚爱 就去挽回她
If you think there's even a chance
that she could be it, you fix it.
Annie让你来劝我的?
Did Annie put you up to this?
谁是Annie?
Who's Annie?
开玩笑呢
I'm kidding.
怎么 我就不能说笑话?
What, I can't joke about this?
- 天哪 老爹            - 我只是不知道怎么做了
- Jesus Christ, Dad.   - I don't know what else to do.
我们走吧
Let's go.
牛排不吃完了?
You don't want to finish your steak?
去他的机场 去他的牛排  走!
We're eating in the goddamn airport.
I can leave the steak. Come on.
是的 是的 我是GQ杂志的Dylan Harper 我们前几个星期见过的
Yeah, hey, this is Dylan Harper from GQ.
We meta few weeks ago at the...
对 对 嘿 能请你帮个忙吗
Right. Hey, can I ask you a huge favor?
- 真对不起 先生        - 我的错
- I am so sorry, sir.  - It's my fault.
- 吓到我了
- 不 不 我的错才是 你没事吧
- You just scared me.
- No, no. My fault. You all right?
- 是的 我没事        - 来 我来帮你
- Yeah, I'm good.   - Here, let me help you with that.
- 谢谢 你真好心
- 好的 祝你旅途顺利
- Thanks, man. You're really nice.
- All right. Hey, safe travels.
- 好的 谢谢                - 谢谢
- All right, thanks, man.  - Okay, thank you.
开什么玩笑 来打一架吧
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
All right, let's dance, Clowny Brown.
- 我怎么惹你了?
- 我看见你跟Jamie一起在酒吧
- What's your problem with me?
- I saw you at that bar with Jamie.
怎么那么好的女孩会跟着你 而不是帅气的我呢
How could such an awesome girl
be with this over this?
我已经喜欢她很多年了
I've been trying to take that little monkey
to pound-town for years.
- 我会向她转告你的问候            - 什么?
- I'll tell her you say hello.   - What?
你头发有点乱 帮你弄好了
You missed a little. There you go.
Dylan 叫到出租车了 快点
Dylan! I got a cab. Come on.
再让我看见你
I ever run into you again,
我就把你宰了炖汤
I'll crush your earlobes
and make soup stock out of them.
- 你想象力真丰富                   -那是
- You have a vivid imagination.  - I do!
- 那我走了                       -那我炖汤去了
- I'm gonna get in the cab now. - I'm gonna go make soup!
- 她怎么了                     - 我不知道
- What's the matter with her?  - I don't know.
天哪 我以为洛杉矶以后够差的了 这里更糟糕
God! I thought LA was bad.
This traffic is terrible.
还有没有其他办法去市里啊
Is there another way into the city?
欠你个大人情 Tommy
I owe you big time, Tommy.
你要报答我哦 事实上 我也正要去市里
You'll make it up to me.
Actually, I was heading into town anyway.
今晚有个聚会 能钓很多男人
Tonight's the Butterfly Ball.
Great place to pick up dudes.
- 你没事的 爸      - 开什么玩笑
- You okay, Dad?  - Are you kidding?
37年的Chris-Craft游艇 没有比这更好的了
1937 Chris-Craft?
Couldn't get any better, buddy.
真棒
Nice.
你好 我是Dylan 我们见过面
Yeah. Hi, this is Dylan. We met at...
是的 能请你帮个忙吗
Right. Can I ask you a huge favor?
这是我的号码 这是遥控器
My number. Here's the remote.
我朋友Dave住对面 他的微波炉坏了 所以他会借用我的厨房
My friend Dave from across the hall, his
oven broke, so he'll be using the kitchen.
你朋友到底是来用厨房还是看着我?
Your friend Dave is here using the kitchen
or watching me?
去吧
Go.
- 我了个..    - 什么?
- Holy...     - What?
"如何穿着白色裤子去烧烤"?
"How to wear white pants to a cookout."
多么经典的文章呀
Did you scoop the Times on this?
I smell Pulitzer.
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.
替我向她问好
Just say hello to her for me, will you?
回头见
See you, Dad.
谢谢
Thanks, man.
你好啊 住对面的Dave
Hi, Dave from across the hall.
你好 Harper先生
Hi, Mr. Harper. How are you?
我知道你为什么在这了
And now we know why you're here.
妈 我在列克星敦的出口这 你在哪
Mom, I'm over by the Lexington exit.
Where are you?
我跟一个系领带的男人站在一起
I'm standing right by the guy in the tie.
- 这有N多系领带的男人啊
- 那就直接找我在哪吧
- There are a million guys in ties.
- So look for the guy I'm standing next to.
你这么做 到底要教我什么
You never do what you say you're gonna do.
When am I gonna learn?
等一下 宝贝
Just hang on, baby.
什么
What?
我想我不会过去了
I don't think I'm gonna be able
to make it after al/.
突然有点事 我们明天见吧
Something came up. Let's meet tomorrow.
到时候我会在你对面的楼梯上
I'll be on the stairs.
Right across from you.
噢 天哪
Oh, my God.
玩得愉快 宝贝
Have a great night, baby.
这是什么?
What is this?
Semisonic 乐队的>
It's Closing Time, by the band Semisonic!
不是> 相信吗
It's not Third Eye Blind.
Can you believe that?
我不是说歌? 是这所有的一切
No, no, no. Not the song. This.
你说让要电影般的生活
You said you wanted your life
to be like a movie.
不得不借用一下真的中央车站了 而不是做个假的
Sorry I had to use the real Grand Central
instead of the fake one.
听着 Jamie 我
Listen, Jamie, I'm...
我听不见你说话!
I'm having trouble hearing you!
是啊 没考虑到这点
Yeah, I didn't really think this through.
拍电影时男人先表白
I guess in the movies
the guy pours his heart out
后期制作时才加的背景音乐
and they put the music in later.
什么?
What?
我搞砸了
I messed up.
我被吓坏了
I was scared.
看看我父母的结局
Look at what happened
with my mom and my dad.
理所当然我很害怕
Of course I was scared.
所以我搞砸了
So I ruined it.
每天发生的点点滴滴
Everything that happens in the day,
我都迫不及待的想告诉Jamie
all I can think to myself is,
"I can't wait to tell Jamie about this."
看到别人在骂人 我想到的 就是你在眨眼
When I see someone cursing,
all I picture is you blinking.
看到有儿童从癌症中康复 我都祈祷那不是那混蛋医生治好的
And when I hear a kid's been cured of
cancer, I pray it's not by that douchebag,
那个甩了你的混蛋医生
tree-hugging fucking doctor
who ran out on you.
我想说 治好癌症固然好 但我希望是别的医生而不是他
I mean, cancer being cured is awesome,
but, you know, I wish someone else did it.
来吧
Come on.
嘿 我好想你
Hey, I miss you.
是啊 我也很想你
Yeah, I miss you, too.
但你说得对 我感情很受伤
But you're not wrong, I am damaged.
我也是 谁不是呢
So am I. Who isn't?
这才让我们很般配
That's what makes us so awesome.
- 还有我们的纹身     - 是啊
- And our tattoos.   - Yeah.
- 不 不 不      - 闭嘴 不是你想的那样
- No, no, no.  - Shut up. It's not what you think.
Jamie 你愿意重新做我的好朋友吗?
Jamie, will you be my best friend again?
- 真逊啊             - 我知道
- That is so lame.   - I know.
白马王子的桥段 不是吗
That's some Prince Charming shit,
though, right?
- 起来吧     - 恩
- Get up.    - Okay.
听着 不和你上床 我也能继续活下去
Look, I can live without
ever having sex with you again.
但那会很难很难
It'd be really hard.
嘿 我只想和好朋友终归于好
Hey, I want my best friend back,
因为我爱上她了
because I'm in love with her.
- 有个条件               - 什么都行
- Under one condition.   - Anything.
吻我
Kiss me.
- 众目睽睽之下?
- 当我没说...
- In public? In front of all these people?
- I did not ask you to...
大家可以回家了
You can all go home now.
那...
Okay. So...
- 现在干嘛             - 我们第一次约会
- What do we do now?  - Have our first date.
好吧
Okay.
噢 天哪 你弄了辆马车?
Oh, my God!
Did you get a horse and carriage?
是啊 不是给你准备的
Yeah, that's not for you.
噢 感谢上帝 我最怕这个了
Oh, thank God.
Horses actually scare the shit out of me.
- 真的?     - 是啊
- Really?   - Yeah.
那..你是哪里人
So, where are you from?
- 费城附近                      - 有意思
- Outside of Philly, actually.  - Interesting.
- 我刚从洛杉矶来纽约
- 有意思 都没问你呢 继续吧
- I'm from LA, just moved to New York.
- Interesting. Didn't really ask, but go on.
什么? 我太激动了 第一次约会 所以...
What? I'm excited, I'm
on a first date. So...
这一点都不奇怪
This isn't weird at all.
- 我们没事了      - 是啊 谢谢你
- We're okay.    - Yeah. Thank you.
所以...
So...
不管了
Yeah, fuck it.